<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<strings>
<string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//GraphicsPreferencesHelp/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The graphics preferences interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. One may customize their graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amout of detail used in rendering certain objects.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of terrain detail you would like to see. 

Sky Detail: Sets the amount of tesselation of the sky dome.  A higher value takes longer to render, but makes the sun look more rounded.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The Preferences &gt; Graphics interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. You may also customize your graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amount of detail or number of triangles used in rendering certain objects. A higher value takes longer to render, but makes these objects appear with more detail.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of detail you would like to see for the terrain texture. 
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans></f_old_trans>
<f_translation>
			세컨드라이프 클라이언트의 그래픽 해상도 및 품질을 제어합니다.  낮음, 중간, 높음, 매우 높음  4단계의 설정을  선택할 수 있습니다. 또한 사용자 크기 확인란을 선택 후 설정을 세부 조작할 수 있습니다.

쉐이더: 쉐이더 유형을 활성화하거나 비활성화합니다. 

반사 디테일: 물에 반사되는 오브젝트 유형을 설정합니다.

아바타 렌더링: 아바타를 렌더링하는 방식의 옵션을 설정합니다.

렌더링 거리 제한: 현재 시점에서 부터 오브젝트가 렌더링되는 거리를 조절합니다.

최대 파티클 수: 화면에서 한 번에 볼 수 있는 최대 파티클 수를 설정합니다.

빛 처리 품질: 빛이 렌더링되는 해상도를 설정합니다. 

메쉬 디테일: 특정 오브젝트를 렌더링하는 디테일 또는 삼각형 개수를 설정합니다. 값이 클수록 렌더링이 더 오래 걸리지만 오브젝트의 모양이 더 자세하게 표현됩니다.

조명 세부 사항: 조명의 유형을 선택합니다.

지형 세부 사항: 지형 텍스처의 디테일을 설정합니다. 
		</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>
			이 창은 창 크기와 클라이언트 그래픽의 해상도 및 품질을 제어합니다.  그래픽 환경 설정 인터페이스를 통해 낮음, 중간, 높음, 매우 높음 등 4개의 그래픽 레벨 중에서 원하는 설정을 선택할 수 있습니다. 사용자 지정 확인란을 선택하고 다음의 설정을 조작하여 이러한 그래픽을 원하는 대로 설정할 수 있습니다.

쉐이더: 여러 가지 픽셀 쉐이더 유형을 활성화하거나 비활성화합니다. 

반사 디테일: 물에 반사될 수 있는 오브젝트 유형을 설정합니다.

아바타 렌더링: 클라이언트가 아바타를 렌더링하는 방식에 영향을 주는 옵션을 설정합니다.

렌더링 거리 제한: 장면에서 현재 시점의 오브젝트가 렌더링되는 거리를 조절합니다.

최대 파티클 수: 화면에서 한 번에 볼 수 있는 최대 파티클 수를 설정합니다.

빛 처리 품질: 빛이 렌더링되는 해상도를 설정합니다. 

메쉬 디테일: 오브젝트를 렌더링하는 디테일을 설정합니다.

조명 세부 사항: 렌더링할 조명 유형을 선택합니다.

지형 세부 사항: 보려는 지형의 디테일을 설정합니다. 
		</f_old_trans>
</string>
</strings>
