<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<strings>
<string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//GraphicsPreferencesHelp/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The graphics preferences interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. One may customize their graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amout of detail used in rendering certain objects.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of terrain detail you would like to see. 

Sky Detail: Sets the amount of tesselation of the sky dome.  A higher value takes longer to render, but makes the sun look more rounded.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The Preferences &gt; Graphics interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. You may also customize your graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amount of detail or number of triangles used in rendering certain objects. A higher value takes longer to render, but makes these objects appear with more detail.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of detail you would like to see for the terrain texture. 
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans></f_old_trans>
<f_translation>
			このパネルはウィンドウのサイズと解像度、およびクライアントのグラフィックの品質を制御します。  [環境設定]&gt;[グラフィック]のインタフェースでは、次の 4 つの中からグラフィック・レベルを選択できます。低、中、高、超高。 また、[カスタム]チェックボックスをクリックし、次の設定を操作することで、グラフィックスの設定をカスタマイズすることもできます。

シェーダー:ピクセル・シェーダーのさまざまな種類を有効または無効にします。 

反射詳細:水が反射するオブジェクトの種類を設定します。

アバター・レンダリング:クライアントによるアバターのレンダリング方法に影響するオプションを設定します。

描画距離:あなたの視点から視界のどのくらいの距離まで、オブジェクトがレンダリングされるかに影響します。

最大パーティクル数:画面に一度に見ることができるパーティクルの最大数を設定します。

ポストプロセス品質:グロー効果(輝き)がレンダリングされる際の解像度を設定します。 

メッシュ詳細: 特定のオブジェクトのレンダリング時の細部表現、または三角形の数を設定します。 値を大きくするほどレンダリングに時間がかかりますが、オブジェクトがより詳細に表示されます。

ライティング詳細:レンダリングする光源の種類を選択します。

地形詳細: 地形テクスチャの細部表現を設定します。 
		</f_translation>

<f_old_trans>
			このパネルはウィンドウのサイズと解像度、およびクライアントのグラフィックの品質を制御します。  グラフィックの環境設定のインタフェースでは、次の 4 つの中からグラフィック・レベルを選択できます。 低、中、高、超高。 ［カスタム］チェックボックをクリックし、次の設定を操作することで、グラフィックスの設定をカスタマイズすることができます。

シェーダー： ピクセル・シェーダーのさまざまな種類を有効または無効にします。 

反射詳細： 水が反射するオブジェクトの種類を設定します。

アバター・レンダリング： クライアントによるアバターのレンダリング方法に影響するオプションを設定します。

描画距離： あなたの視点から視界のどのくらいの距離まで、オブジェクトがレンダリングされるかに影響します。

最大パーティクル数： 画面に一度に見ることができるパーティクルの最大数を設定します。

ポストプロセス品質： グロー効果（輝き）がレンダリングされる際の解像度を設定します。 

メッシュ詳細： 特定のオブジェクトのレンダリング時の細部表現を設定します。

ライティング詳細： レンダリングする光源の種類を選択します。

地形詳細: 地形の細部表現を設定します。 
		</f_old_trans>
</string>
</strings>
