<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<strings>
<string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotDeedLandNoRegion/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to deed land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Help -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to deed land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Tools -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法转让土地:
无法找到此土地所属的区域。
请使用帮助 -&gt; 报告漏洞来报告此项错误。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotButLandRegionNotFound/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to buy land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Help -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to buy land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Tools -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法购买土地:
无法找到该土地所在区域。
请使用帮助 -&gt; 报告漏洞来向我们报告这项错误。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotReleaseLandRegionNotFound/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to abandon land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Help -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to abandon land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Tools -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法放弃土地:
无法找到此土地所属的区域。
请使用帮助 -&gt; 报告漏洞来报告这个错误。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotDivideLandNoRegion/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to divide land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Help -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to divide land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Tools -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法划分土地:
 无法找到土地所属区域。
请使用帮助 -&gt; 报告漏洞来报告此项错误。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotJoinLandNoRegion/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to join land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Help -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to join land:
Cannot find the region this land is in.
Please use Tools -&gt; Report Bug to report this.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法连接土地:
无法找到该土地所属的区域.
请使用帮助 -&gt; 报告程序漏洞,让我们知道问题所在.
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//CannotSaveToAssetStore/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Unable to save [NAME] to central asset store.
This is usually a temporary failure. Please
customize and save the wearable again in a
few minutes. If this problem persists, please
click on the &apos;Help | Report Bug&apos; pull down menu
and provide details about your network setup.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Unable to save [NAME] to central asset store.
This is usually a temporary failure. Please
customize and save the wearable again in a
few minutes. If this problem persists, please
click on the &apos;Tools | Report Bug&apos; pull down menu
and provide details about your network setup.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			无法储存[NAME]至终属资产存储.
这通常是暂时性功能障碍。请用户化后再次保存。
如果问题依然存在，请点击
帮助/报告漏洞并提供
客户网络设置的具体信息。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//AddFriend/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Friends can track each other on the map and 
will receive online status updates. 
 
Offer friendship to [NAME]?
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Friends can give permissions to 
track each other on the map and 
receive online status updates. 
 
Offer friendship to [NAME]?
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			好友们可以在地图上互相追踪，并可以在线接受更新信息. 
 
是否发送友谊卡给[NAME]?
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//DownloadMacMandatory/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			A new version of [SECOND_LIFE] is available.
[MESSAGE]
 
You must download this update to use the system.
 
Download to your Applications folder?
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			A new version of [SECOND_LIFE] is available.
[MESSAGE]

You must download this update to use the system.
 
Download to your Applications folder?
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			[SECOND_LIFE]有新版本可用。
[MESSAGE]
 
你必须下再次更新才能运行系统。
是否下载更新至应用软件文件夹?
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//AddClassified/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Classified ads appear in the &apos;Classified&apos; section of the
Search directory for one week.
 
Fill out your ad, then click &apos;Publish...&apos; to add it to the
directory.
 
You&apos;ll be asked for a price to pay when clicking Publish.
Paying more makes your ad appear higher in the list, and
also appear higher when people search for keywords.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Classified ads appear in the &apos;Classified&apos; section of the
Find directory for one week.
 
Fill out your ad, then click &apos;Publish...&apos; to add it to the
directory.
 
You&apos;ll be asked for a price to pay when clicking Publish.
Paying more makes your ad appear higher in the list, and
also appear higher when people search for keywords.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			分类广告会在查找名录的&apos;Classified&apos;栏目里保留一周时间。

 
填写你的广告,然后点击&apos;发布...&apos;，既添加广告至广告名录中。
当点击发布时，你将被要求支付发布广告费用. 大额支付意味着你的广告会在名单较前的地方出现，并且当用关键词查找时，你的广告也出现在查询结果较高的位置上。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//HelpEstateExternallyVisible</b_path>
<c_attribute>title</c_attribute>
<d_old>Visible From Mainland</d_old>
<e_new>Public Access</e_new>
<f_old_trans>从大陆可视</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//HelpEstateExternallyVisible/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Sets whether residents who are in the Linden owned &apos;mainland&apos; 
estates can see your estate on the world map. 
 
Default: on
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Sets whether residents who are on other estates can enter this
			 estate without being on an access list.
 
Default: on
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			设置在林登所拥有的&apos;大陆&apos;领地内的居民 
是否能从地图上看到你的领地。 
 
默认:可以
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//HelpReportBug/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Use this tool to report technical features that do not perform 
as described or expected. All bug reports are investigated and 
resolved. No email response will be sent, you may reply to the 
auto-response email to add more details to your report. 
If you are having a technical difficulty, please contact Support at: 
 
http://secondlife.com/community/support.php
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Use this tool to *only* report technical features that do not perform as 
described or expected, please provide as much detail as possible, You 
may reply to the auto-response email to add more details to your report.
All bug reports are investigated and assessed. No email response will be sent.
-
If you are having a technical difficulty, please contact Support at: 
http://secondlife.com/community/support.php
-
Note: Incomplete reports will not be investigated
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			Use this tool to report technical features that do not perform 
as described or expected. All bug reports are investigated and 
resolved. No email response will be sent, you may reply to the 
auto-response email to add more details to your report. 
If you are having a technical difficulty, please contact Support at: 
 
http://secondlife.com/community/support.php
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_about.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floater_about/credits_editor</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW and many others.

Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: Kyrah Abattoir, Icesis Anansi, Clifton Antonelli, Nargus Asturias, Justizin Austinmer, Drake Bacon, Bitzer Balderdash, McWheelie Baldwin, SuezanneC Baskerville, Sweetheart Baskerville, Logan Bauer, Malarthi Behemoth, phoenix Behemoth, Eva Bellambi, Samgame Bertrand, Woody Blair, Tin Bling, Bibi Book, Barney Boomslang, Eric Boyer, Chromal Brodsky, Kerian Bunin, Lara Bunin, BigRick Byrd, Jillian Callahan, Hypatia Callisto, Frans Charming, nathalie Christensen, Francis Chung, pizzaguy Clutterbuck, Evo Commons, Entity Cosmo, Grazel Cosmo, Tiger Crossing, Fremont Cunningham, Jaki Daligdig, Sugar Darling, Todd David, Norman Desmoulins, Gxeremio Dimsum, Happy Dimsum, Kim Dingo, Roy Domela, Cory Edo, Delu Elytis, DBDigital Epsilon, Leeza Everett, Garth FairChang, Snowflake Fairymeadow, Khamon Fate, lex Fitzcarraldo, Kitto Flora, Angel Fluffy, CrystalShard Foo, Raudf Fox, Govindira Galatea, Rizpah Galatea, Tre Giles, Gattz Gilman, Kex Godel, Armandi Goodliffe, Tsu Goodliffe, Nickolas Goodman, Damen Gorilla, Nytemyst Grace, Mhaijik Guillaume, Gleeb Gupte, Ebonfire Harbinger, Bethanee Heaney, Jenny Hicks, Sandling Honey, Victoria Jacques, Adso Krogstad, Travis Lambert, simon Lameth, Duffy Langdon, Aaron Levy, Jade Lily, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Lola Lollipop, Michi Lumin, KaiLastOfTheBrunnenG Macdonald, Jesse Malthus, Herry Maltz, Seth Mandelbrot, Raavi Mann, Shirley Marquez, Dnate Mars, Ima Mechanique, Hawk Mendicant, Mercury Metropolitan, Haravikk Mistral, Trent Mondrian, Nexus Nash, Seraph Nephilim, Lewis Nerd, Aurael Neurocam, Lex Neva, Prokofy Neva, Seagel Neville, Kate Nicholas, Didde Nielsen, Richard Noonan, crevan Nori, Maczter Oddfellow, vanler Odets, Fat Ogre, Hamncheese Omlet, Strife Onizuka, Panthar Orlowski, Jessica Ornitz, Ron Overdrive, OmniCron Overlord, Dargon Pacer, Kar Parks, Eloise Pasteur, Caliandris Pendragon, Julianna Pennyfeather, Iron Perth, Shawk Pertwee, Mera Pixel, Elle Pollack, Phoenix Psaltery, Hank Ramos, Jon Ree, Tam Ree, Zi Ree, Jon Rolland, BamBam Sachertorte, kai Sachertorte, Mily Sartre, ice Semple, Desmond Shang, DigiKatt Shaw, Felix Sholokhov, Rhyph Somme, Rain Soothsayer, Oz Spade, squeekachu Spearmann, Wesley Spengler, Belaya Statosky, eltee Statosky, Khashai Steinbeck, Draco Steinhardt, Hope Stilman, Ashen Stygian, Seifert Surface, Gigs Taggart, Dolmere Talamasca, JayJay Talamasca, Becky Tardis, Fenris Tardis, Cubey Terra, Osprey Therian, Millie Thompson, John Toonie, Charlene Trudeau, Lyr Tuppakaka, Indy Turner, Luthien Unsung, Random Unsung, Huns Valen, Valdemar Virgo, Gordon Wendt, Mike Westerburg, Wayfinder Wishbringer, Lee Wormser, Aimee Xia, nimrod Yaffle, Yiffy Yaffle, Elle74 Zaftig and many others.


APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
Cg Copyright (C) 2002, NVIDIA Corporationa.
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.


It&apos;s not a glitch, it&apos;s a feature.
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, JillS, Yool, Jane and many others.

Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: Atte Aderdeen, Alise Altman, Doomby Arrow, Rox Arten, Jesse Barnett, Smiley Barry, SuezanneC Baskerville, Glitch Braess, Dorian Caldwell, JuiceBox132 Castro, Aden Christensen, Fremont Cunningham, Zirnitra Demar, Errafel Eccleston, Cory Edo, Kitto Flora, Ashrilyn Hayashida, Elektra Hesse, Friar Jeffries, Samuel Jordan, DeLisa Junot, Howie Lament, Candide LeMay, Michi Lumin, Ikani Mahana, SignpostMarv Martin, Ksathra Mason, Console Mission, Haravikk Mistral, Usagi Musashi, Lex Neva, Jamma Newt, Blaze Nielsen, Destiny Niles, Tateru Nino, Harald Nomad, Nerk Noonan, Stumbelina Ophelia, Fledhyris Proudhon, Londyn Reatequi, Zi Ree, Hank Rucker, BamBam Sachertorte, kai Sachertorte, Sean Sao, Funk Schnook, Magnum Serpentine, Nekosune Smails, Rhyph Somme, Al Sonic, Oz Spade, Wesley Spengler, Steve Steed, Gearsawe Stonecutter, Dirk Talamasca, Dolmere Talamasca, John Taylor, Raymond Tuxing, Churchill Tweak, Huns Valen, windozer Vargas, Sabby Whiplash, Raven Wombat, Beatfox Xevious, Yiffy Yaffle, Alpha Zaius, Hewee Zetkin, Jai Zucker and many others.


APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
Cg Copyright (C) 2002, NVIDIA Corporationa.
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.


Don&apos;t hassle the hoff.
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		第二人生的推出应感谢以下人物的贡献： Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW and many others.

感谢以下居民，他们的帮助保证了这次第二人生的版本是有史以来最出色的: Kyrah Abattoir, Icesis Anansi, Clifton Antonelli, Nargus Asturias, Justizin Austinmer, Drake Bacon, Bitzer Balderdash, McWheelie Baldwin, SuezanneC Baskerville, Sweetheart Baskerville, Logan Bauer, Malarthi Behemoth, phoenix Behemoth, Eva Bellambi, Samgame Bertrand, Woody Blair, Tin Bling, Bibi Book, Barney Boomslang, Eric Boyer, Chromal Brodsky, Kerian Bunin, Lara Bunin, BigRick Byrd, Jillian Callahan, Hypatia Callisto, Frans Charming, nathalie Christensen, Francis Chung, pizzaguy Clutterbuck, Evo Commons, Entity Cosmo, Grazel Cosmo, Tiger Crossing, Fremont Cunningham, Jaki Daligdig, Sugar Darling, Todd David, Norman Desmoulins, Gxeremio Dimsum, Happy Dimsum, Kim Dingo, Roy Domela, Cory Edo, Delu Elytis, DBDigital Epsilon, Leeza Everett, Garth FairChang, Snowflake Fairymeadow, Khamon Fate, lex Fitzcarraldo, Kitto Flora, Angel Fluffy, CrystalShard Foo, Raudf Fox, Govindira Galatea, Rizpah Galatea, Tre Giles, Gattz Gilman, Kex Godel, Armandi Goodliffe, Tsu Goodliffe, Nickolas Goodman, Damen Gorilla, Nytemyst Grace, Mhaijik Guillaume, Gleeb Gupte, Ebonfire Harbinger, Bethanee Heaney, Jenny Hicks, Sandling Honey, Victoria Jacques, Adso Krogstad, Travis Lambert, simon Lameth, Duffy Langdon, Aaron Levy, Jade Lily, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Lola Lollipop, Michi Lumin, KaiLastOfTheBrunnenG Macdonald, Jesse Malthus, Herry Maltz, Seth Mandelbrot, Raavi Mann, Shirley Marquez, Dnate Mars, Ima Mechanique, Hawk Mendicant, Mercury Metropolitan, Haravikk Mistral, Trent Mondrian, Nexus Nash, Seraph Nephilim, Lewis Nerd, Aurael Neurocam, Lex Neva, Prokofy Neva, Seagel Neville, Kate Nicholas, Didde Nielsen, Richard Noonan, crevan Nori, Maczter Oddfellow, vanler Odets, Fat Ogre, Hamncheese Omlet, Strife Onizuka, Panthar Orlowski, Jessica Ornitz, Ron Overdrive, OmniCron Overlord, Dargon Pacer, Kar Parks, Eloise Pasteur, Caliandris Pendragon, Julianna Pennyfeather, Iron Perth, Shawk Pertwee, Mera Pixel, Elle Pollack, Phoenix Psaltery, Hank Ramos, Jon Ree, Tam Ree, Zi Ree, Jon Rolland, BamBam Sachertorte, kai Sachertorte, Mily Sartre, ice Semple, Desmond Shang, DigiKatt Shaw, Felix Sholokhov, Rhyph Somme, Rain Soothsayer, Oz Spade, squeekachu Spearmann, Wesley Spengler, Belaya Statosky, eltee Statosky, Khashai Steinbeck, Draco Steinhardt, Hope Stilman, Ashen Stygian, Seifert Surface, Gigs Taggart, Dolmere Talamasca, JayJay Talamasca, Becky Tardis, Fenris Tardis, Cubey Terra, Osprey Therian, Millie Thompson, John Toonie, Charlene Trudeau, Lyr Tuppakaka, Indy Turner, Luthien Unsung, Random Unsung, Huns Valen, Valdemar Virgo, Gordon Wendt, Mike Westerburg, Wayfinder Wishbringer, Lee Wormser, Aimee Xia, nimrod Yaffle, Yiffy Yaffle, Elle74 Zaftig and many others.


APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
Cg Copyright (C) 2002, NVIDIA Corporationa.
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

All rights reserved.  查看licenses.txt获取细节.


这不是一次故障，而是一个特性.
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_about_land.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floaterland/landtab/land_options_panel/edit objects check</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Create Objects</d_old>
<e_new>All Residents</e_new>
<f_old_trans>创造东东</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_about_land.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floaterland/landtab/land_options_panel/check other scripts</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Run Other Scripts</d_old>
<e_new>All Residents</e_new>
<f_old_trans>运行其它脚本</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_about_land.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floaterland/landtab/land_options_panel/check group scripts</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Run Group Scripts</d_old>
<e_new>Group</e_new>
<f_old_trans>运行社团脚本</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_chat_history.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/chat floater/Mute resident</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Mute resident</d_old>
<e_new>Mute</e_new>
<f_old_trans>屏蔽居民</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_directory.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/directory/Directory Tabs/popular_panel/These are the most popular places in the world, as measured by traffic,         the amount of time people spend there.</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
				These are the most popular places in the world, as measured by traffic,
	the amount of time people spend there.
			</d_old>
<e_new>
				These are the most popular places in the world, as measured by traffic,
the amount of time people spend there.
			</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
				这里有在第二人生世界里最流行的场所，由交通状况，和人们在那里花费的时间长短来衡量。
			</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_friends.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/friends/im_btn</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>IM...</d_old>
<e_new>IM</e_new>
<f_old_trans>即时通...</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_friends.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/friends/offer_teleport_btn</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Offer Teleport...</d_old>
<e_new>Teleport...</e_new>
<f_old_trans>提供闪电传送...</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_friends.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/friends/profile_btn</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Profile...</d_old>
<e_new>Profile</e_new>
<f_old_trans>档案...</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_instant_message.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/im_floater/live_help_dialog</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		*** Welcome to Live Help, where our wonderful volunteers assist their fellow Residents with Second Life! *** 
Please first check our SL Help Pages by pressing F1. 
If your answer isn&apos;t there, please enter your question to begin, then allow a few moments for available helpers to respond. 
Please don&apos;t close Live Help until you&apos;re finished. If you don&apos;t hear back, you can always try again later. 
NOTE: Live Helpers aren&apos;t Linden employees, so unless a person responding has the last name &apos;Linden&apos;, answers should be considered unofficial.
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		*** Welcome to Help Request *** 
Please first check our SL Help Pages by pressing F1, or by accessing the Knowledge Base http://secondlife.com/knowledgebase/ 
If your answer is not there, please enter your question to begin, then allow a few moments for available helpers to respond.
-=-=- Response times will vary, especially during peak times -=-=-
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		*** 欢迎来到在线帮助站,在这里，我们出色的志愿者们会协助他们的第二人生居民朋友们在第二人生里精彩的生活！ *** 
请先按F1键，进入第二人生帮助页面。如果你想要的答案不在这里，请键入你的问题，点击开始，等候若干分钟后，在线的帮助者会给你回复。
如果您的处理过程没有结束，请不要关闭在线帮助站的页面。如果您没有得到回应，你可以一直选择重新尝试一遍。 
注意: 在线帮助者并不是林登实验室的雇员, 所以，除非回应人的姓氏为&apos;Linden&apos;,否则回复都应视为非正式的.
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_preview_notecard.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/preview notecard/Notecard Editor</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Loading...
	</d_old>
<e_new>
Loading...
</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		请等待...
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_report_abuse.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floater_report_abuse/sim_title</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Simulator:
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Region:
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		模拟器:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_report_bug.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/bug_reporter/dscr_title</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Details:
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Details: (Please provide as much information as possible)
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		详细:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_report_bug.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/bug_reporter/details_edit</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Steps to reproduce the bug:

Observed results:

Expected results:
	</d_old>
<e_new>Steps to reproduce the bug:

Observed results:

Expected results:
    </e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		修复漏洞的途径：:

观察的结果：:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_report_bug.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/bug_reporter/bug_aviso</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		If this bug allows you to do something you should not be able 
to do, especially if it impacts performance or security, please 
select the &apos;Exploit&apos; category. Thank you!
	</d_old>
<e_new>
Note: Incomplete reports will not be investigated
If this bug allows you to do something you should not be able 
to do, especially if it impacts performance or security, please 
select the &apos;Exploit&apos; category. Thank you!
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		If this bug allows you to do something you should not be able 
to do, especially if it impacts performance or security, please 
select the &apos;Exploit&apos; category. Thank you!
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_script_ed_panel.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/script panel/Script Editor</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Loading...
	</d_old>
<e_new>
Loading...
</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		请等待...
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_top_objects.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/top_objects/id_text</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Object ID:
	</d_old>
<e_new>
Object ID:
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		东东ID:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>floater_world_map.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/worldmap/location</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Search by Region Name
	</d_old>
<e_new></e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		按地区名搜索
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>notify.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//OfferFriendship/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			[NAME] is offering friendship.
 
You will be able to track each other on
the map and will receive online status
updates.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			[NAME] is offering friendship.
      
      By default, you will be able to 
see each other&apos;s online status.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			[NAME]正在发送好友邀请.
 
你可以通过地图追踪彼此，并将收到好友在线状态更新。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>notify.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//FirstSandbox/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			This is a sandbox region.
Objects you build here may be deleted after you 
leave the area, and the region will be wiped 
every [HOURS] hours starting at [TIME] AM Pacific Time.
 
Sandbox regions are uncommon, and are marked with signs.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			This is a sandbox region.
Objects you build here may be deleted after
you leave the area, Sandboxes clean on a regular basis, please refer to the information at the top of the screen next to the region name.
 
Sandbox regions are uncommon, and are marked with signs.
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			这是一块沙盒区域。
在这里创建的东东将在其离开这里后被删除，且此区域将每[HOURS]小时抹去一次所创建东东，始于太平洋时间早上[TIME].
 
沙盒区域并不常见, 并会有特殊标识标出。
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_avatar.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Panel Avatar/tab/2nd Life/online_yes</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
				Online: Yes
			</d_old>
<e_new>
				Currently Online
			</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
				是否在线: 是
			</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_media_remote.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/music_remote/text</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Movie control
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Movies
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		电影控制
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_music_remote.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/music_remote/text</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Music control
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Music
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		音乐控制
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_chat.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/chat/arrow_keys_move_avatar_check</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Arrow keys move avatar when chatting</d_old>
<e_new>Arrow keys always move avatar when chatting</e_new>
<f_old_trans>；聊天时可用箭头键移动你的化身</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_general.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/general_panel/language_combobox/Chinese</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Chinese
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Chinese - Beta
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			中文
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_general.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/general_panel/language_combobox/Deutsch(German)</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			Deutsch (German)
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			Deutsch (German) - Beta
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			Deutsch (German)
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_general.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/general_panel/language_combobox/(Japanese)</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			日本語 (Japanese)
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			日本語 (Japanese) - Beta
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			日本語 (Japanese)
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_general.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/general_panel/language_combobox/(Korean)</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			한국어 (Korean)
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			한국어 (Korean) - Beta
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
			한국어 (Korean)
		</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_im.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/im</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>IM</d_old>
<e_new>Communication</e_new>
<f_old_trans>即时通</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_im.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/im/text_box</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		IM Options:
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Profile Online Status:
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		即时通选项:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_preferences_im.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/im/text_box2</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Busy Mode Response:
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		IM Options:
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		忙碌模式的自动回复:
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_estate.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Estate/externally_visible_check</b_path>
<c_attribute>label</c_attribute>
<d_old>Visible From Mainland</d_old>
<e_new>Public Access</e_new>
<f_old_trans>从大陆可视</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/detail_texture_text</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Detail Textures (requires 512x512, 24 bit .tga files)
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Terrain Textures (requires 512x512, 24 bit .tga files)
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		详细质地（要求512*512（分辨率），24bit.tga文件格式。
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl5</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		1 (Low)
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Texture Elevation Ranges
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		1 (低)
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl6</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		2
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Southwest
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		2
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl7</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		3
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Northwest
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		3
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl8</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		4 (High)
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Southeast
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		4 (高)
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl9</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Texture Elevation Ranges
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Northeast
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		材质范围
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl10</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Southwest
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		These values represent the blend range for the textures above.
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		西南
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl11</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Northwest
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		Measured in meters, the LOW value is the MAXIMUM height of Texture #1,
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		西北
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_region_texture.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/Textures/height_text_lbl12</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Southeast
	</d_old>
<e_new>
		and the HIGH value is the MINIMUM height of Texture #4.
	</e_new>
<f_old_trans>
		东南
	</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string><string><a_file>panel_toolbar.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/panel_toolbar/chat_btn</b_path>
<c_attribute>tool_tip</c_attribute>
<d_old>Talk to people nearby. Click Chat then History to see what has been said.</d_old>
<e_new>Talk to people nearby. (Enter)</e_new>
<f_old_trans>与附近的人交谈.点击交谈之后点击历史去查找交谈记录。</f_old_trans>
<f_translation/></string>
</strings>
