<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<strings>
<string>
<a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//ClickWebProfileHelpAvatar/message</b_path>
<c_attribute/>
<d_old>

			If this resident has a web profile URL set then you can:
 * Click Load to load the page with the embedded web browser.
 * Click Open to view externally in your default web browser.
 
When viewing your profile you can enter any URL as your Web Profile.
Residents can visit the URL you specify when they view your profile.
		
</d_old>
<e_new>

			If this resident has set a web profile URL then you can:
 * Click "Load" to load the page with the embedded web browser.
 * Click Load->"Open in external browser" to view externally.
 * Click Load->"Home URL" to return to resident's web profile if you've navigated away.
 
When viewing your own profile you can enter any URL as your web profile and click OK to set it.
Other residents can visit the URL you set when they view your profile.
		
</e_new>
<f_translation>

			この住人がウェブプロフィールURLを設定している場合は、以下のことが可能です。
 * そのページを内蔵ブラウザーで表示するには、[ロード]をクリックします。
 * そのページを外部ブラウザーで表示するには、[ロード]-[開く]をクリックします。
 * 別のページにアクセスしてしまい、住人のウェブ・プロフィールに戻りたい時は、[ロード]-[ホームURL]をクリックします。
 
自分のプロフィールを表示しているときは、任意のURLをウェブプロフィールとして入力し、[OK]をクリックして設定できます。
プロフィールを見た他の住人は、そのURLにアクセスすることができます。
		
</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>

			この住人がウェブ・プロフィールURLを設定している場合は、以下のことが可能です。
*そのページを内蔵ブラウザーで表示するには、[ロード]をクリックします。
*そのページをデフォルトの外部ウェブ・ブラウザーで表示するには、[開く]をクリックします。
 
自分のプロフィールを表示しているときは、任意のURLをウェブ・プロフィールとして入力できます。
プロフィールを見た住人は、そのURLにアクセスすることができます。
		
</f_old_trans>
</string>
<string>
<a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//HelpReportAbuseContainsCopyright/message</b_path>
<c_attribute/>
<d_old>

			Dear Resident,
 
Reports about copyright infringement can only be submitted
as described at http://secondlife.com/corporate/dmca.php.

Reports concerning copyright infringement will automatically
be discarded if they are submitted through the 'Abuse Report'
feature. If your report does not relate to copyright infringement,
you may close this window and finish submitting your report.
 
Thank you,
 
Linden Lab
		
</d_old>
<e_new>

			Dear Resident,

If you are reporting intellectual property infringement, please make sure you are reporting it correctly:

(1) The Abuse Process. You may submit an abuse report if you believe a Resident is exploiting the Second Life permissions system, for example, by using CopyBot or similar copying tools, to infringe intellectual property rights. The Abuse Team investigates and issues appropriate disciplinary action for behavior that violates the Second Life Community Standards or Terms of Service. However, the Abuse Team does not handle and will not respond to requests to remove content from the Second Life world.

(2) The DMCA or Content Removal Process. To request removal of content from Second Life, you must submit a valid notification of infringement as provided in our DMCA Policy at http://secondlife.com/corporate/dmca.php.

If you still wish to continue with the abuse process, please close this window and finish submitting your report.

Thank you,

Linden Lab
</e_new>
<f_translation>

			親愛なる住人の皆様へ

知的所有権の侵害を報告する場合は、以下のとおり正確に報告してください。

(1) 嫌がらせの処理。 住人がSecond Lifeの許可システムを不当に使用し、知的所有権が侵害されていると考えられる場合は、嫌がらせ報告を提出することができます。許可システムを不当に使用する手段としては、たとえば、CopyBotまたは類似したコピー・ツールがあります。 嫌がらせ対応担当チームが調査を行い、Second Lifeのコミュニティ・スタンダードまたは利用規約に違反する態度に対しては適切な懲罰処分が行われます。 ただし、嫌がらせ対応担当チームでは、コンテンツをSecond Lifeワールドから削除するリクエストに対する処理または回答は行いません。

(2) DMCAまたはコンテンツの削除処理。 Second Lifeからのコンテンツの削除をリクエストするには、http://secondlife.com/corporate/dmca.phpのDMCAポリシーにある、侵害に関する有効な通知を提出する必要があります。

嫌がらせの処理を継続する場合は、このウインドウを閉じ、報告を提出してください。

ご協力ありがとうございます。

Linden Lab
</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>

			親愛なる住人の皆様へ：
 
著作権侵害に関する報告はhttp://secondlife.com/corporate/dmca.phpの
記述に従ってのみ提出することができます。

[嫌がらせ報告]機能を通じて著作権侵害に関する報告を提出しても、その報告は自動的に破棄されます。著作権侵害に関係のない報告であれば、このウィンドウを閉じて報告を提出することができます。
 
ご協力ありがとうございます。
 
Linden Lab
		
</f_old_trans>
</string>
<string>
<a_file>floater_about.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floater_about/credits_editor</b_path>
<c_attribute/>
<d_old>

  Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Tofu, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Jill, Yool, Jane, Yuki, Yoz, Matthew, Arthur, Jennifer, Karl, Brian, Ben, Janine, Christopher, Madhavi, Everett, Anthony, Joon, Jake, sean, Adreanne, Stephany, KellyJo, Jeremy, Pramod, Joshua, Sean, Christopher, Amy, Ceren, Katherine, jon, Sudheendra, James, Stephan, Kari, Kartic, Todd, Thomas, Joki, Rebecca, Belinda, Bert, Roger, Bridie, Kristi, Brian, Maria, John, Aric, Nathanel, Melinda, Darrell, Jennifer, Sandy, Greg, Rob, Brad, Chris, Eric, Palmer, Asi, Katja, Lisa, Minda, Jen, Aaron, Bryan, Mark, Jonathan, Jamie, Laurel, William, Matthew, Steve, David, Remy, James, Tim, Lee, Brian, Ashlei, Sam, Mike, Ethan, Austin, Wanda, Paul, Brian, Rachel, Valentyn, Emma Williams, Autum, Steven, Laley, Charles, Jessica, Sue, Gillian, CG, Kip, Kristen, Shamiran, Blake, Brett, Erica, Kent, Joel, Plexus, Twilight, Joppa, Enus, Kraft, Naveen, Simon, Q, Ronp, Laurap, Ram, KyleJM, Marty, Kend, Daveh, Prospero, Melissa, Nat, Hamilton, Green, Seraph, Ekim, Miz, Jimmy, Kosmo, Rome, Doris, JT, Benoc, Whump, Mango, Trinity, Patch, TJ, Christy, Bao, Joohwan, Kate, Oreh, Angela, Johan, Cheah, Lan, Matias, Brandy, Cogsworth, Aleks,  Mitchell, Space, Einstein, Bambers, Colton, Malbers, Maggie, Umesh, Santosh, Rose, Stash, Rothman, Winnie, Stella, Niall and many others.

  Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: aaron23 decuir, Abelv Vollmar, Abyssin Otoro, ActingIll Igaly, Adamas Carter, Addy Broome, Adelia Menges, Alexandra Rucker, Alexandrea Fride, Alissa Sabre, Alyx Jonson, Ann Otoole, Anton Fargis, Aradia Dielli, Araina jewell, Arcane Clawtooth, arcangelo vantelli, Are Sperber, Argent Stonecutter, arkady yost, Ashcroft Burnham, Ashen Arida, Auron Forcella, Azadine Umarov, Azildin Furst, Balp Allen, Balpien Hammerer, Barney Boomslang, Barrett Slade, becky pippen, Beeflin Grut, Beer Dailey, Behemoth Greenwood, bigmanu greene, bitova loon, Bonca Chikuwa, Bonnie Bechir, Brandon Catteneo, buttonpusher jones, Carina Raymaker, Ceera Murakami, Celierra Darling, ChatNoir Moonsoo, Cheetah Hammerer, chet neurocam, Cinthya Loveless, Cold Spitteler, Coral Quinnell, Crash Pointe, CrazyTB Oh, Creem Pye, Crom Chaffe, ctrl althouse, dade carver, Dael Ra, dakota schwade, Dale Innis, Damian McLeod, Danger Lytton, danielluh ashton, DanOfWA Flanagan, Davec Horsforth, Davidius Morigi, davie zinner, Day Oh, DBDigital Epsilon, Deany Fall, deBruce Munro, Decaf Coffey, Dedric Mauriac, Deeso Saeed, Dekka Raymaker, dexter eberhart, Dildo Spitz, Dizzy Banjo, djcabello klaar, Dnali Anabuki, Domchi Underwood, Doran Zemlja, Drew Dwi, Duckless Vandyke, Duncan Stenvaag, Dylan Rickenbacker, dzogchen Moody, Dzonatas Sol, Eddy Stryker, Edward Griffith, Edward Pearse, ein duesenburg, Elle Pollack, Elle74 Zaftig, Emileigh Starbrook, Emma Nowhere, ener bing, Erdrick Balbozar, eric domela, Evangeline Biedermann, Excalibur Longstaff, Fake Fitzgerald, Feldspar Millgrove, Feynt Mistral, Fluf Fredriksson, Forbid Utorid, Fortyniner Beck, Francesco Despres, Francisco Koolhoven, Franta Burt, Fury Rosewood, garde Burrel, Garmin Kawaguichi, Gavin Ichigo, Gellan Glenelg, Genie Demina, Gennifer Meredith, Gigs Taggart, Goldie Katsu, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Haravikk Mistral, Harleen Gretzky, Haruki Watanabe, Heather Manatiso, Henri Beauchamp, Honey Fairweather, Hypatia Callisto, Ice Brodie, icktoofay Kamachi, IntLibber Brautigan, Janise Dreamscape, Jay Shinobu, Jenni Ryba, Jeremy Ondricek, JetZep Zabelin, Jims Smythe, Jini Hammerer, Jopy Weber, JustOneMore Loon, Kaluura Boa, Kara Markova, Kevin Susenko, Khyra Ares, Kii Lilliehook, Kitty Barnett, Kris Kuttelwascher, Lanita Wingtips, Laura18 Streeter, Lee Ludd, Lettrius Jewell, Liberty Tesla, LilyAnna Carter, Lindal Kidd, Lisa Lowe, Lisa McConnell, Lola Machin, luca peck, Lupus Clawtooth, M1sha Dallin, Macsima Dagostino, Mana Janus, Mani Canning, Manjusri Binder, marceledward edman, march Korda, marchino villota, Marcus Llewellyn, MartinRJ Fayray, Matthew Dowd, Max Kleiber, mazzy fastback, McCabe Maxsted, Mckailen Kohnke, Meghan Dench, Melvin Starbrook, Mercia Mcmahon, Miakoda Carnell, Michelle2 Zenovka, Michi Lumin, mick parnall, Milla Michinaga, Millie Thompson, miranda Ashby, Mircea Lobo, MIssSara Beck, mouse mimistrobell, Myria Boa, Nanci Barthelmess, Nargus Asturias, Natalya Debevec, Nedrae Messmer, Nexeus Fatale, Niky Zenovka, Nimrod Szondi, Ninane Yoshikawa, Noch Tripsa, nokithecat writer, Nyko Merlin, Onyx Halberd, oryx tempel, Osprey Therian, Pac Hyun, Panagea McMillan, Patrick Ferrentino, PattehPh0x Katsu, ponk bing, Poppy Linden, Prajna Vella, Precious Rhiano, Prokofy Neva, Randall Lovenkraft, Rascal Ratelle, Raydon Writer, Rhaorth Antonelli, Rock Hayek, Ron Crimson, Ron Khondji, Ronald Richez, Rui Clary, Ruud Lathrop, Sakkano Imako, Sam Reinard, Sascha Vandyke, Scrippy Scofield, Sean18 McCarey, Sedona Mills, Sekonda Huet, Seraph Nephilim, Sergei Milos, Shadowquine Maltz, shai khalifa, sheilah flatley, Sheri Underwood, Shuggy Husky, Sierra Janus, Sigma Avro, Simil Miles, simon kline, Simon Nolan, Sindy Tsure, Sparks Keynes, Squirrel Wood, Stahi Columbia, StarSong Bright, Summer Seale, Sunn Thunders, Susan Koltai, Syler Zhora, Synack Fitzgerald, Tayra Dagostino, Tee Cramer, Teravus Ousley, Thomas Shikami, Tia Araw, Tillie Ariantho, Topher Brooks, Torley Linden, Twosteppin Jewell, tx Oh, urantia jewell, vaguegirl Petty, VeC Merlin, venus petrov, vv33d Beck, vynka dean, zann canto, zeebster colasanti, Zi Ree, Zion Tristan, Zorin Frobozz, Zyzzy Zarf

  3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
  APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
  cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
  expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
  FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
  GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
  Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
  jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
  jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
  ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
  OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
  SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
  SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
  xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
  zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

  All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.

  Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  Happiness is a warm puppy. -- Charles M. Schulz
</d_old>
<e_new>

  Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Tessa, Andrew, Cory, Ben, Bunny, Char, Charlie, Colin, Dan, Daniel, Doug, Eric, Hamlet, Haney, Hunter, Ian, Jeff, Jim, John, Lee, Mark, Peter, Phoenix, Richard, Robin, Xenon, Steve, Tanya, Eddie, Frank, Bruce, Aaron, Alice, Bob, Debra, Eileen, Helen, Janet, Louie, Leviathania, Stefan, Ray, Kevin, Tom, Mikeb, MikeT, Burgess, Elena, Tracy, BillTodd, Ryan, Zach, Sarah, Nova, Otakon, Tim, Stephanie, Michael, Evan, Nicolas, Catherine, Rachelle, Dave, Holly, Bub, Kelly, Magellan, Ramzi, Don, Sabin, Jill, Rheya, DanceStar, Jeska, Hungry, Torley, Kona, Callum, Charity, Ventrella, Jack, Uncle, Vektor, Iris, Chris, Nicole, Mick, Reuben, Blue, Babbage, Yedwab, Deana, Lauren, Brent, Pathfinder, Chadrick, Altruima, Jesse, Monroe, David, Tess, Lizzie, Patsy, Pony, Isaac, Lawrence, Cyn, Bo, Gia, Annette, Marius, Tbone, Jonathan, Karen, Ginsu, Yuko, Makiko, Thomas, Harry, Seth, Alexei, Brian, Guy, Runitai, Ethan, Data, Cornelius, Kenny, Swiss, Zero, Natria, Wendy, Stephen, Teeple, Thumper, Lucy, Dee, Mia, Liana, Warren, Branka, Aura, beez, Milo, Hermia, Red, Thrax, Joe, Sally, Magenta, Paul, Jose, Rejean, Henrik, Lexie, Amber, Logan, Xan, Nora, Morpheus, Donovan, Leyla, MichaelFrancis, Beast, Cube, Bucky, Joshua, Stryfe, Harmony, Teresa, Claudia, Walker, Glenn, Fritz, Fordak, June, Cleopetra, Jean, Ivy, Betsy, Roosevelt, Spike, Ken, Which, Tofu, Chiyo, Rob, Zee, dustin, George, Del, Matthew, Cat, Jacqui, Lightfoot, Adrian, Viola, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Sunil, Yool, Rika, Jane, Xtreme, Frontier, a2, Neo, Siobhan, Yoz, Justin, Elle, Qarl, Benjamin, Isabel, Gulliver, Everett, Christopher, Izzy, Stephany, Garry, Sejong, Sean, Tobin, Iridium, Meta, Anthony, Jeremy, JP, Jake, Maurice, Madhavi, Leopard, Kyle, Joon, Kari, Bert, Belinda, Jon, Kristi, Bridie, Pramod, KJ, Socrates, Maria, Ivan, Aric, Yamasaki, Adreanne, Jay, MitchK, Ceren, Coco, Durl, Jenny, Periapse, Kartic, Storrs, Lotte, Sandy, Colossus, Zen, BigPapi, Brad, Pastrami, Kurz, Mani, Neuro, Jaime, MJ, Rowan, Sgt, Elvis, Gecko, Samuel, Sardonyx, Leo, Bryan, Niko, Soft, Poppy, Rachel, Aki, Angelo, Banzai, Alexa, Sue, CeeLo, Bender, CG, Gillian, Pelle, Nick, Echo, Zara, Christine, Shamiran, Emma, Blake, Keiko, Plexus, Joppa, Sidewinder, Erica, Ashlei, Twilight, Kristen, Brett, Q, Enus, Simon, Bevis, Kraft, Kip, Chandler, Ron, LauraP, Ram, KyleJM, Scouse, Prospero, Melissa, Marty, Nat, Hamilton, Kend, Lordan, Jimmy, Kosmo, Seraph, Green, Ekim, Wiggo, JT, Rome, Doris, Miz, Benoc, Whump, Trinity, Patch, Kate, TJ, Bao, Joohwan, Christy, Sofia, Matias, Cogsworth, Johan, Oreh, Cheah, Angela, Brandy, Mango, Lan, Aleks, Gloria, Heidy, Mitchell, Space, Colton, Bambers, Einstein, Maggie, Malbers, Rose, Winnie, Stella, Milton, Rothman, Niall, Marin, Allison, James, Katie, Dawn, Katt, Kalpana, Judy, Andrea, Ambroff, Infinity, Gail, Rico, Raymond, Yi, William, Christa, M, Teagan, Scout, Molly, Dante, Corr, Dynamike, Usi, Kaylee, Lil, Danica, Sascha, Kelv, Jacob, Nya, Rodney, Brandon, Elsie, Blondin, Grant, Katrin, Nyx, Gabriel, Locklainn, Claire, Devin, Minerva, Monty, Austin, Bradford, Si, Keira, H, Caitlin, Dita, Makai, Jenn and many others.

  Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: aaron23 decuir, Abra Miles, absolute balderdash, adelle fitzgerald, Aeron Kohime, Aki Shichiroji, Alger Meads, Alissa Sabre, AlwaysIcey Mapholisto, Arawn Spitteler, Aren Mandala, Arianna Wrigglesworth, Bagushii Kohime, Balpien Hammerer, Blinking2342 Blinker, byakuya runo, Capucchy Streeter, Chandra Jun, Coyote Pace, Crusher Soderstrom, Cummere Mayo, cyberrosa Rossini, Dael Ra, danana dodonpa, Darek Deluca, Davec Horsforth, django yifu, draco crane, Dre Dagostino, Ephyu Reino, etan quan, Fenrix Murakami, Fledhyris Proudhon, Fred Wardhani, Frederich Courier, garth fairchang, Gellan Glenelg, Geraldine Giha, GOLAN Eilde, gonzo joubert, Hachiro Yokosuka, Hampton Hax, harleywood guru, Hevenz Vansant, imnotgoing sideways, Jaden Giles, Jeanette Janus, Karl Dorance, keaton Akina, Khashai Steinbeck, KiPSOFT Tuqiri, kirstenlee Cinquetti, Kitty Barnett, Laurent Vesta, Lazure Ryba, Lima Vesperia, Linzi Bingyi, Lisa Lowe, LuDon Ninetails, Mark Rosenbaum, McCabe Maxsted, Michi Lumin, Midi Aeon, ml0rtd kit, Mo Eriksen, Morice Flanagan, Mysterion Aeon, Nad Gough, norgan torok, Pygar Bu, Qie Niangao, rachel corleone, Rado Arado, roberto salubrius, Royer Pessoa, samia bechir, Sasha Nurmi, Sean Heying, Selkit Diller, Shadow Pidgeon, simon kline, Smokie Ember, Soap Clawtooth, Strife Onizuka, Tal Chernov, Talan Hyun, tangletwigs fairymeadow, Tanya Spinotti, Tayra Dagostino, Teebone Aeon, Theremes Langdon, Thraxis Epsilon, tucor Capalini, Vasko Hawker, VenusMari Zapedzki, Vex Streeter, Viktoria Dovgal, Vincent Nacon, Viridian Exonar, Vivienne Schell, WarKirby Magojiro, Wilton Lundquist, Yukinoroh Kamachi, Zyzzy Zarf

  3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
  APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
  cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
  expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
  FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
  GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
  Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
  jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
  jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
  ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
  OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
  SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
  SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
  xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
  zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

  All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.

  Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  What happens to a dream deferred? --Langston Hughes
</e_new>
<f_translation>

  Second Lifeは、Philip、Tessa、Andrew、Cory、Ben、Bunny、Char、Charlie、Colin、Dan、Daniel、Doug、Eric、Hamlet、Haney、Hunter、Ian、Jeff、Jim、John、Lee、Mark、Peter、Phoenix、Richard、Robin、Xenon、Steve、Tanya、Eddie、Frank、Bruce、Aaron、Alice、Bob、Debra、Eileen、Helen、Janet、Louie、Leviathania、Stefan、Ray、Kevin、Tom、Mikeb、MikeT、Burgess、Elena、Tracy、BillTodd、Ryan、Zach、Sarah、Nova、Otakon、Tim、Stephanie、Michael、Evan、Nicolas、Catherine、Rachelle、Dave、Holly、Bub、Kelly、Magellan、Ramzi、Don、Sabin、Jill、Rheya、DanceStar、Jeska、Hungry、Torley、Kona、Callum、Charity、Ventrella、Jack、Uncle、Vektor、Iris、Chris、Nicole、Mick、Reuben、Blue、Babbage、Yedwab、Deana、Lauren、Brent、Pathfinder、Chadrick、Altruima、Jesse、Monroe、David、Tess、Lizzie、Patsy、Pony、Isaac、Lawrence、Cyn、Bo、Gia、Annette、Marius、Tbone、Jonathan、Karen、Ginsu、Yuko、Makiko、Thomas、Harry、Seth、Alexei、Brian、Guy、Runitai、Ethan、Data、Cornelius、Kenny、Swiss、Zero、Natria、Wendy、Stephen、Teeple、Thumper、Lucy、Dee、Mia、Liana、Warren、Branka、Aura、beez、Milo、Hermia、Red、Thrax、Joe、Sally、Magenta、Paul、Jose、Rejean、Henrik、Lexie、Amber、Logan、Xan、Nora、Morpheus、Donovan、Leyla、MichaelFrancis、Beast、Cube、Bucky、Joshua、Stryfe、Harmony、Teresa、Claudia、Walker、Glenn、Fritz、Fordak、June、Cleopetra、Jean、Ivy、Betsy、Roosevelt、Spike、Ken、Which、Tofu、Chiyo、Rob、Zee、dustin、George、Del、Matthew、Cat、Jacqui、Lightfoot、Adrian、Viola、Alfred、Noel、Irfan、Sunil、Yool、Rika、Jane、Xtreme、Frontier、a2、Neo、Siobhan、Yoz、Justin、Elle、Qarl、Benjamin、Isabel、Gulliver、Everett、Christopher、Izzy、Stephany、Garry、Sejong、Sean、Tobin、Iridium、Meta、Anthony、Jeremy、JP、Jake、Maurice、Madhavi、Leopard、Kyle、Joon、Kari、Bert、Belinda、Jon、Kristi、Bridie、Pramod、KJ、Socrates、Maria、Ivan、Aric、Yamasaki、Adreanne、Jay、MitchK、Ceren、Coco、Durl、Jenny、Periapse、Kartic、Storrs、Lotte、Sandy、Colossus、Zen、BigPapi、Brad、Pastrami、Kurz、Mani、Neuro、Jaime、MJ、Rowan、Sgt、Elvis、Gecko、Samuel、Sardonyx、Leo、Bryan、Niko、Soft、Poppy、Rachel、Aki、Angelo、Banzai、Alexa、Sue、CeeLo、Bender、CG、Gillian、Pelle、Nick、Echo、Zara、Christine、Shamiran、Emma、Blake、Keiko、Plexus、Joppa、Sidewinder、Erica、Ashlei、Twilight、Kristen、Brett、Q、Enus、Simon、Bevis、Kraft、Kip、Chandler、Ron、LauraP、Ram、KyleJM、Scouse、Prospero、Melissa、Marty、Nat、Hamilton、Kend、Lordan、Jimmy、Kosmo、Seraph、Green、Ekim、Wiggo、JT、Rome、Doris、Miz、Benoc、Whump、Trinity、Patch、Kate、TJ、Bao、Joohwan、Christy、Sofia、Matias、Cogsworth、Johan、Oreh、Cheah、Angela、Brandy、Mango、Lan、Aleks、Gloria、Heidy、Mitchell、Space、Colton、Bambers、Einstein、Maggie、Malbers、Rose、Winnie、Stella、Milton、Rothman、Niall、Marin、Allison、James、Katie、Dawn、Katt、Kalpana、Judy、Andrea、Ambroff、Infinity、Gail、Rico、Raymond、Yi、William、Christa、M、Teagan、Scout、Molly、Dante、Corr、Dynamike、Usi、Kaylee、Lil、Danica、Sascha、Kelv、Jacob、Nya、Rodney、Brandon、Elsie、Blondin、Grant、Katrin、Nyx、Gabriel、Locklainn、Claire、Devin、Minerva、Monty、Austin、Bradford、Si、Keira、H、Caitlin、Dita、Makai、Jennと、その他多数の人達によって作成されました。

  このバージョンをこれまでで最高のものになるようご協力をいただいた以下の住人の皆様に深く感謝いたします。 aaron23 decuir、Abra Miles、absolute balderdash、adelle fitzgerald、Aeron Kohime、Aki Shichiroji、Alger Meads、Alissa Sabre、AlwaysIcey Mapholisto、Arawn Spitteler、Aren Mandala、Arianna Wrigglesworth、Bagushii Kohime、Balpien Hammerer、Blinking2342 Blinker、byakuya runo、Capucchy Streeter、Chandra Jun、Coyote Pace、Crusher Soderstrom、Cummere Mayo、cyberrosa Rossini、Dael Ra、danana dodonpa、Darek Deluca、Davec Horsforth、django yifu、draco crane、Dre Dagostino、Ephyu Reino、etan quan、Fenrix Murakami、Fledhyris Proudhon、Fred Wardhani、Frederich Courier、garth fairchang、Gellan Glenelg、Geraldine Giha、GOLAN Eilde、gonzo joubert、Hachiro Yokosuka、Hampton Hax、harleywood guru、Hevenz Vansant、imnotgoing sideways、Jaden Giles、Jeanette Janus、Karl Dorance、keaton Akina、Khashai Steinbeck、KiPSOFT Tuqiri、kirstenlee Cinquetti、Kitty Barnett、Laurent Vesta、Lazure Ryba、Lima Vesperia、Linzi Bingyi、Lisa Lowe、LuDon Ninetails、Mark Rosenbaum、McCabe Maxsted、Michi Lumin、Midi Aeon、ml0rtd kit、Mo Eriksen、Morice Flanagan、Mysterion Aeon、Nad Gough、norgan torok、Pygar Bu、Qie Niangao、rachel corleone、Rado Arado、roberto salubrius、Royer Pessoa、samia bechir、Sasha Nurmi、Sean Heying、Selkit Diller、Shadow Pidgeon、simon kline、Smokie Ember、Soap Clawtooth、Strife Onizuka、Tal Chernov、Talan Hyun、tangletwigs fairymeadow、Tanya Spinotti、Tayra Dagostino、Teebone Aeon、Theremes Langdon、Thraxis Epsilon、tucor Capalini、Vasko Hawker、VenusMari Zapedzki、Vex Streeter、Viktoria Dovgal、Vincent Nacon、Viridian Exonar、Vivienne Schell、WarKirby Magojiro、Wilton Lundquist、Yukinoroh Kamachi、Zyzzy Zarf

  3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
  APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
  cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
  expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
  FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
  GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
  Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
  jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
  jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
  ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
  OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
  SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
  SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
  xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
  zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

  無断転写、複製、転載を禁じます。  詳細はlicenses.txtを参照してください。

  Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  後回しにされた夢はどうなるの? --ラングストン・ヒューズ
</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>

		Second Life は、 Philip、 Tessa、 Andrew、 Cory、 Ben、 Bunny、 Char、 Charlie、 Colin、 Dan、 Daniel、 Doug、 Eric、 Hamlet、 Haney、 Hunter、 Ian、 Jeff、 Jim、 John、 Lee、 Mark、 Peter、 Phoenix、 Richard、 Robin、 Xenon、 Steve、 Tanya、 Eddie、 Frank、 Bruce、 Aaron、 Alice、 Bob、 Debra、 Eileen、 Helen、 Janet、 Louie、 Leviathania、 Stefan、 Ray、 Kevin、 Tom、 Mikeb、 MikeT、 Burgess、 Elena、 Tracy、 BillTodd、 Ryan、 Zach、 Sarah、 Nova、 Otakon、 Tim、 Stephanie、 Michael、 Evan、 Nicolas、 Catherine、 Rachelle、 Dave、 Holly、 Bub、 Kelly、 Magellan、 Ramzi、 Don、 Sabin、 Jill、 Rheya、 DanceStar、 Jeska、 Hungry、 Torley、 Kona、 Callum、 Charity、 Ventrella、 Jack、 Uncle、 Vektor、 Iris、 Chris、 Nicole、 Mick、 Reuben、 Blue、 Babbage、 Yedwab、 Deana、 Lauren、 Brent、 Pathfinder、 Chadrick、 Altruima、 Jesse、 Monroe、 David、 Tess、 Lizzie、 Patsy、 Pony、 Isaac、 Lawrence、 Cyn、 Bo、 Gia、 Annette、 Marius、 Tbone、 Jonathan、 Karen、 Ginsu、 Yuko、 Makiko、 Thomas、 Harry、 Seth、 Alexei、 Brian、 Guy、 Runitai、 Ethan、 Data、 Cornelius、 Kenny、 Swiss、 Zero、 Natria、 Wendy、 Stephen、 Teeple、 Thumper、 Lucy、 Dee、 Mia、 Liana、 Warren、 Branka、 Aura、 beez、 Milo、 Hermia、 Red、 Thrax、 Joe、 Sally、 Magenta、 Paul、 Jose、 Rejean、 Henrik、 Lexie、 Amber、 Logan、 Xan、 Nora、 Morpheus、 Donovan、 Leyla、 MichaelFrancis、 Beast、 Cube、 Bucky、 Joshua、 Stryfe、 Harmony、 Teresa、 Claudia、 Walker、 Glenn、 Fritz、 Fordak、 June、 Cleopetra、 Jean、 Ivy、 Betsy、 Roosevelt、 Spike、 Ken、 Which、 Tofu、 Chiyo、 Rob、 Zee、 dustin、 George、 Del、 Matthew、 Cat、 Jacqui、 Lightfoot、 Adrian、 Viola、 Alfred、 Noel、 Irfan、 Sunil、 Yool、 Rika、 Jane、 Xtreme、 Frontier、 a2、 Neo、 Siobhan、 Yoz、 Justin、 Elle、 Qarl、 Benjamin、 Isabel、 Gulliver、 Everett、 Christopher、 Izzy、 Stephany、 Garry、 Sejong、 Sean、 Tobin、 Iridium、 Meta、 Anthony、 Jeremy、 JP、 Jake、 Maurice、 Madhavi、 Leopard、 Kyle、 Joon、 Kari、 Bert、 Belinda、 Jon、 Kristi、 Bridie、 Pramod、 KJ、 Socrates、 Maria、 Ivan、 Aric、 Yamasaki、 Adreanne、 Jay、 MitchK、 Ceren、 Coco、 Durl、 Jenny、 Periapse、 Kartic、 Storrs、 Lotte、 Sandy、 Colossus、 Zen、 BigPapi、 Brad、 Pastrami、 Kurz、 Mani、 Neuro、 Jaime、 MJ、 Rowan、 Sgt、 Elvis、 Gecko、 Samuel、 Sardonyx、 Leo、 Bryan、 Niko、 Soft、 Poppy、 Rachel、 Aki、 Angelo、 Banzai、 Alexa、 Sue、 CeeLo、 Bender、 CG、 Gillian、 Pelle、 Nick、 Echo、 Zara、 Christine、 Shamiran、 Emma、 Blake、 Keiko、 Plexus、 Joppa、 Sidewinder、 Erica、 Ashlei、 Twilight、 Kristen、 Brett、 Q、 Enus、 Simon、 Bevis、 Kraft、 Kip、 Chandler、 Ron、 LauraP、 Ram、 KyleJM、 Scouse、 Prospero、 Melissa、 Marty、 Nat、 Hamilton、 Kend、 Lordan、 Jimmy、 Kosmo、 Seraph、 Green、 Ekim、 Wiggo、 JT、 Rome、 Doris、 Miz、 Benoc、 Whump、 Trinity、 Patch、 Kate、 TJ、 Bao、 Joohwan、 Christy、 Sofia、 Matias、 Cogsworth、 Johan、 Oreh、 Cheah、 Angela、 Brandy、 Mango、 Lan、 Aleks、 Gloria、 Heidy、 Mitchell、 Space、 Colton、 Bambers、 Einstein、 Maggie、 Malbers、 Rose、 Winnie、 Stella、 Milton、 Rothman、 Niall、 Marin、 Allison、 James、 Katie、 Dawn、 Katt、 Kalpana、 Judy、 Andrea、 Ambroff、 Infinity、 Gail、 Rico、 Raymond、 Yi、 William、 Christa、 M、 Teagan、 Scout、 Molly、 Dante、 Corr、 Dynamike、 Usi、 Kaylee、 Lil、 Danica、 Sascha、 Kelv、 Jacob、 Nya、 Rodney、 Brandon、 Elsie、 Blondin、 Grant、 Katrin、 Nyx、 Gabriel、 Locklainn、 Claire、 Devin、 Minerva、 Monty、 Austin、 Bradford、 Si、 Keira、 H、 Caitlin、 Dita、 Makai、 Jenn と、その他多数の人達によって作成されました。

このバージョンをこれまでで最高のものになるようご協力をいただいた以下の住人の皆様に深く感謝いたします。aaron23 decuir、 Abra Miles、 absolute balderdash、 adelle fitzgerald、 Aeron Kohime、 Aki Shichiroji、 Alger Meads、 Alissa Sabre、 AlwaysIcey Mapholisto、 Arawn Spitteler、 Aren Mandala、 Arianna Wrigglesworth、 Bagushii Kohime、 Balpien Hammerer、 Blinking2342 Blinker、 byakuya runo、 Capucchy Streeter、 Chandra Jun、 Coyote Pace、 Crusher Soderstrom、 Cummere Mayo、 cyberrosa Rossini、 Dael Ra、 danana dodonpa、 Darek Deluca、 Davec Horsforth、 django yifu、 draco crane、 Dre Dagostino、 Ephyu Reino、 etan quan、 Fenrix Murakami、 Fledhyris Proudhon、 Fred Wardhani、 Frederich Courier、 garth fairchang、 Gellan Glenelg、 Geraldine Giha、 GOLAN Eilde、 gonzo joubert、 Hachiro Yokosuka、 Hampton Hax、 harleywood guru、 Hevenz Vansant、 imnotgoing sideways、 Jaden Giles、 Jeanette Janus、 Karl Dorance、 keaton Akina、 Khashai Steinbeck、 KiPSOFT Tuqiri、 kirstenlee Cinquetti、 Kitty Barnett、 Laurent Vesta、 Lazure Ryba、 Lima Vesperia、 Linzi Bingyi、 Lisa Lowe、 LuDon Ninetails、 Mark Rosenbaum、 McCabe Maxsted、 Michi Lumin、 Midi Aeon、 ml0rtd kit、 Mo Eriksen、 Morice Flanagan、 Mysterion Aeon、 Nad Gough、 norgan torok、 Pygar Bu、 Qie Niangao、 rachel corleone、 Rado Arado、 roberto salubrius、 Royer Pessoa、 samia bechir、 Sasha Nurmi、 Sean Heying、 Selkit Diller、 Shadow Pidgeon、 simon kline、 Smokie Ember、 Soap Clawtooth、 Strife Onizuka、 Tal Chernov、 Talan Hyun、 tangletwigs fairymeadow、 Tanya Spinotti、 Tayra Dagostino、 Teebone Aeon、 Theremes Langdon、 Thraxis Epsilon、 tucor Capalini、 Vasko Hawker、 VenusMari Zapedzki、 Vex Streeter、 Viktoria Dovgal、 Vincent Nacon、 Viridian Exonar、 Vivienne Schell、 WarKirby Magojiro、 Wilton Lundquist、 Yukinoroh Kamachi、 Zyzzy Zarf

3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

無断複写・転載を禁じます。詳細はlicenses.txtを参照してください。

Voice chat Audio coding:Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec.G.722.1 Annex C)


しあわせはあったかい子犬-- チャールズ・M・シュルツ
	
</f_old_trans>
</string>
</strings>
