<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<strings>
<string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//HelpRegionObjectBonus/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			The Object Bonus is a multiplier for primitives allowed on any given
parcel. The range allowed is 1 to 10. Set at &apos;1&apos;, each 512m2 parcel
is allowed 117 objects. Set at &apos;2&apos;, each 512m2 parcel is
allowed 234, or twice as many, and so on. The max number of objects
allowed per region remains 15,000 no matter what the
Object Bonus is. once set, be aware that lowering the Object Bonus may cause
objects to be returned or deleted. 
 
Default: 1.0
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			The Object Bonus is a multiplier for primitives allowed on any given
parcel. The range allowed is 1 to 10. Set at &apos;1&apos;, each 512m2 parcel
is allowed 117 objects. Set at &apos;2&apos;, each 512m2 parcel is
allowed 234, or twice as many, and so on. The max number of objects
allowed per region remains 15,000 no matter what the
Object Bonus is. Once set, be aware that lowering the Object Bonus may cause objects to be returned or deleted. 
 
Default: 1.0
		</e_new>
<f_translation>
			오브젝트 보너스는 특정 구획에 허락된 프림에 대해 배로
증가합니다. 허용 범위는 1에서 10입니다. &apos;1&apos;로 설정했을 때 각 512m2 구획에
117 개 오브젝트가 허용됩니다. &apos;2&apos;로 설정하면 각 512m2 구획에 허용되는
오브젝트는 두 배인 234개로 됩니다. 지역당 허용되는
최대 오브젝트 수는 오브젝트 보너스에 상관없이 15,000 개
입니다. 일단 설정한 후 오브젝트 보너스를 낮추게 되면 오브젝트가반환되거나 삭제될 수 있는점을 알아 두십시오. 
 
기본 설정: 1.0
		</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>
			오브젝트 보너스는 특정 구획에 허락된 프림에 대해 배로
증가합니다. 허용 범위는 1에서 10입니다. &apos;1&apos;로 설정했을 때 각 512m2 구획에
허용되는 오브젝트는 117개입니다. &apos;2&apos;로 설정하면 각 512m2 구획에 허용되는
오브젝트가 두 배인 234개로 됩니다. 지역당 허용되는
오브젝트의 최대 개수는 오브젝트 보너스에 대해 설정된 값과 상관없이
15,000개입니다. 이 값을 설정한 후에는, 값 변경으로 인해
현재 구획 내의 오브젝트가 반환되거나 삭제될 것이 확실하기 전까지는
이 값을 낮추면 안됩니다.
 
기본 설정: 1.0
		</f_old_trans>
</string><string><a_file>floater_about.xml</a_file>
<b_path>/floater_about/credits_editor</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
		Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Tofu, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Jill, Yool, Jane, Yuki, Yoz, Matthew, Arthur, Jennifer, Karl, Brian, Ben, Janine, Christopher, Madhavi, Everett, Anthony, Joon, Jake, sean, Adreanne, Stephany, KellyJo, Jeremy, Pramod, Joshua, Sean, Christopher, Amy, Ceren, Katherine, jon, Sudheendra, James, Stephan, Kari, Kartic, Todd, Thomas, Joki, Rebecca, Belinda, Bert, Roger, Bridie, Kristi, Brian, Maria, John, Aric, Nathanel, Melinda, Darrell, Jennifer, Sandy, Greg, Rob, Brad, Chris, Eric, Palmer, Asi, Katja, Lisa, Minda, Jen, Aaron, Bryan, Mark, Jonathan, Jamie, Laurel, William, Matthew, Steve, David, Remy, James, Tim, Lee, Brian, Ashlei, Sam, Mike, Ethan, Austin, Wanda, Paul, Brian, Rachel, Valentyn, Emma Williams, Autum, Steven, Laley, Charles, Jessica, Sue, Gillian, CG, Kip, Kristen, Shamiran, Blake, Brett, Erica, Kent, Joel, Plexus, Twilight, Joppa, Enus, Kraft, Naveen, Simon, Q, Ronp, Laurap, Ram, KyleJM, Marty, Kend, Daveh, Prospero, Melissa, Nat, Hamilton, Green, Seraph, Ekim, Miz, Jimmy, Kosmo, Rome, Doris, JT, Benoc, Whump, Mango, Trinity, Patch, TJ, Christy, Bao, Joohwan, Kate, Oreh, Angela, Johan, Cheah, Lan, Matias, Brandy, Cogsworth, Aleks,  Mitchell, Space, Einstein, Bambers, Colton, Malbers, Maggie, Umesh, Santosh, Rose, Stash, Rothman, Winnie, Stella, Niall and many others.

Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: aaron23 decuir, Abelv Vollmar, Abyssin Otoro, ActingIll Igaly, Adamas Carter, Addy Broome, Adelia Menges, Alexandra Rucker, Alexandrea Fride, Alissa Sabre, Alyx Jonson, Ann Otoole, Anton Fargis, Aradia Dielli, Araina jewell, Arcane Clawtooth, arcangelo vantelli, Are Sperber, Argent Stonecutter, arkady yost, Ashcroft Burnham, Ashen Arida, Auron Forcella, Azadine Umarov, Azildin Furst, Balp Allen, Balpien Hammerer, Barney Boomslang, Barrett Slade, becky pippen, Beeflin Grut, Beer Dailey, Behemoth Greenwood, bigmanu greene, bitova loon, Bonca Chikuwa, Bonnie Bechir, Brandon Catteneo, buttonpusher jones, Carina Raymaker, Ceera Murakami, Celierra Darling, ChatNoir Moonsoo, Cheetah Hammerer, chet neurocam, Cinthya Loveless, Cold Spitteler, Coral Quinnell, Crash Pointe, CrazyTB Oh, Creem Pye, Crom Chaffe, ctrl althouse, dade carver, Dael Ra, dakota schwade, Dale Innis, Damian McLeod, Danger Lytton, danielluh ashton, DanOfWA Flanagan, Davec Horsforth, Davidius Morigi, davie zinner, Day Oh, DBDigital Epsilon, Deany Fall, deBruce Munro, Decaf Coffey, Dedric Mauriac, Deeso Saeed, Dekka Raymaker, dexter eberhart, Dildo Spitz, Dizzy Banjo, djcabello klaar, Dnali Anabuki, Domchi Underwood, Doran Zemlja, Drew Dwi, Duckless Vandyke, Duncan Stenvaag, Dylan Rickenbacker, dzogchen Moody, Dzonatas Sol, Eddy Stryker, Edward Griffith, Edward Pearse, ein duesenburg, Elle Pollack, Elle74 Zaftig, Emileigh Starbrook, Emma Nowhere, ener bing, Erdrick Balbozar, eric domela, Evangeline Biedermann, Excalibur Longstaff, Fake Fitzgerald, Feldspar Millgrove, Feynt Mistral, Fluf Fredriksson, Forbid Utorid, Fortyniner Beck, Francesco Despres, Francisco Koolhoven, Franta Burt, Fury Rosewood, garde Burrel, Garmin Kawaguichi, Gavin Ichigo, Gellan Glenelg, Genie Demina, Gennifer Meredith, Gigs Taggart, Goldie Katsu, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Haravikk Mistral, Harleen Gretzky, Haruki Watanabe, Heather Manatiso, Henri Beauchamp, Honey Fairweather, Hypatia Callisto, Ice Brodie, icktoofay Kamachi, IntLibber Brautigan, Janise Dreamscape, Jay Shinobu, Jenni Ryba, Jeremy Ondricek, JetZep Zabelin, Jims Smythe, Jini Hammerer, Jopy Weber, JustOneMore Loon, Kaluura Boa, Kara Markova, Kevin Susenko, Khyra Ares, Kii Lilliehook, Kitty Barnett, Kris Kuttelwascher, Lanita Wingtips, Laura18 Streeter, Lee Ludd, Lettrius Jewell, Liberty Tesla, LilyAnna Carter, Lindal Kidd, Lisa Lowe, Lisa McConnell, Lola Machin, luca peck, Lupus Clawtooth, M1sha Dallin, Macsima Dagostino, Mana Janus, Mani Canning, Manjusri Binder, marceledward edman, march Korda, marchino villota, Marcus Llewellyn, MartinRJ Fayray, Matthew Dowd, Max Kleiber, mazzy fastback, McCabe Maxsted, Mckailen Kohnke, Meghan Dench, Melvin Starbrook, Mercia Mcmahon, Miakoda Carnell, Michelle2 Zenovka, Michi Lumin, mick parnall, Milla Michinaga, Millie Thompson, miranda Ashby, Mircea Lobo, MIssSara Beck, mouse mimistrobell, Myria Boa, Nanci Barthelmess, Nargus Asturias, Natalya Debevec, Nedrae Messmer, Nexeus Fatale, Niky Zenovka, Nimrod Szondi, Ninane Yoshikawa, Noch Tripsa, nokithecat writer, Nyko Merlin, Onyx Halberd, oryx tempel, Osprey Therian, Pac Hyun, Panagea McMillan, Patrick Ferrentino, PattehPh0x Katsu, ponk bing, Poppy Linden, Prajna Vella, Precious Rhiano, Prokofy Neva, Randall Lovenkraft, Rascal Ratelle, Raydon Writer, Rhaorth Antonelli, Rock Hayek, Ron Crimson, Ron Khondji, Ronald Richez, Rui Clary, Ruud Lathrop, Sakkano Imako, Sam Reinard, Sascha Vandyke, Scrippy Scofield, Sean18 McCarey, Sedona Mills, Sekonda Huet, Seraph Nephilim, Sergei Milos, Shadowquine Maltz, shai khalifa, sheilah flatley, Sheri Underwood, Shuggy Husky, Sierra Janus, Sigma Avro, Simil Miles, simon kline, Simon Nolan, Sindy Tsure, Sparks Keynes, Squirrel Wood, Stahi Columbia, StarSong Bright, Summer Seale, Sunn Thunders, Susan Koltai, Syler Zhora, Synack Fitzgerald, Tayra Dagostino, Tee Cramer, Teravus Ousley, Thomas Shikami, Tia Araw, Tillie Ariantho, Topher Brooks, Torley Linden, Twosteppin Jewell, tx Oh, urantia jewell, vaguegirl Petty, VeC Merlin, venus petrov, vv33d Beck, vynka dean, zann canto, zeebster colasanti, Zi Ree, Zion Tristan, Zorin Frobozz, Zyzzy Zarf

APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.

Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


Happiness is a warm puppy. -- Charles M. Schulz
	</d_old>
<e_new>
  Second Life is brought to you by Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Tofu, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Jill, Yool, Jane, Yuki, Yoz, Matthew, Arthur, Jennifer, Karl, Brian, Ben, Janine, Christopher, Madhavi, Everett, Anthony, Joon, Jake, sean, Adreanne, Stephany, KellyJo, Jeremy, Pramod, Joshua, Sean, Christopher, Amy, Ceren, Katherine, jon, Sudheendra, James, Stephan, Kari, Kartic, Todd, Thomas, Joki, Rebecca, Belinda, Bert, Roger, Bridie, Kristi, Brian, Maria, John, Aric, Nathanel, Melinda, Darrell, Jennifer, Sandy, Greg, Rob, Brad, Chris, Eric, Palmer, Asi, Katja, Lisa, Minda, Jen, Aaron, Bryan, Mark, Jonathan, Jamie, Laurel, William, Matthew, Steve, David, Remy, James, Tim, Lee, Brian, Ashlei, Sam, Mike, Ethan, Austin, Wanda, Paul, Brian, Rachel, Valentyn, Emma Williams, Autum, Steven, Laley, Charles, Jessica, Sue, Gillian, CG, Kip, Kristen, Shamiran, Blake, Brett, Erica, Kent, Joel, Plexus, Twilight, Joppa, Enus, Kraft, Naveen, Simon, Q, Ronp, Laurap, Ram, KyleJM, Marty, Kend, Daveh, Prospero, Melissa, Nat, Hamilton, Green, Seraph, Ekim, Miz, Jimmy, Kosmo, Rome, Doris, JT, Benoc, Whump, Mango, Trinity, Patch, TJ, Christy, Bao, Joohwan, Kate, Oreh, Angela, Johan, Cheah, Lan, Matias, Brandy, Cogsworth, Aleks,  Mitchell, Space, Einstein, Bambers, Colton, Malbers, Maggie, Umesh, Santosh, Rose, Stash, Rothman, Winnie, Stella, Niall and many others.

  Thank you to the following residents for helping to ensure that this is the best version yet: aaron23 decuir, Abelv Vollmar, Abyssin Otoro, ActingIll Igaly, Adamas Carter, Addy Broome, Adelia Menges, Alexandra Rucker, Alexandrea Fride, Alissa Sabre, Alyx Jonson, Ann Otoole, Anton Fargis, Aradia Dielli, Araina jewell, Arcane Clawtooth, arcangelo vantelli, Are Sperber, Argent Stonecutter, arkady yost, Ashcroft Burnham, Ashen Arida, Auron Forcella, Azadine Umarov, Azildin Furst, Balp Allen, Balpien Hammerer, Barney Boomslang, Barrett Slade, becky pippen, Beeflin Grut, Beer Dailey, Behemoth Greenwood, bigmanu greene, bitova loon, Bonca Chikuwa, Bonnie Bechir, Brandon Catteneo, buttonpusher jones, Carina Raymaker, Ceera Murakami, Celierra Darling, ChatNoir Moonsoo, Cheetah Hammerer, chet neurocam, Cinthya Loveless, Cold Spitteler, Coral Quinnell, Crash Pointe, CrazyTB Oh, Creem Pye, Crom Chaffe, ctrl althouse, dade carver, Dael Ra, dakota schwade, Dale Innis, Damian McLeod, Danger Lytton, danielluh ashton, DanOfWA Flanagan, Davec Horsforth, Davidius Morigi, davie zinner, Day Oh, DBDigital Epsilon, Deany Fall, deBruce Munro, Decaf Coffey, Dedric Mauriac, Deeso Saeed, Dekka Raymaker, dexter eberhart, Dildo Spitz, Dizzy Banjo, djcabello klaar, Dnali Anabuki, Domchi Underwood, Doran Zemlja, Drew Dwi, Duckless Vandyke, Duncan Stenvaag, Dylan Rickenbacker, dzogchen Moody, Dzonatas Sol, Eddy Stryker, Edward Griffith, Edward Pearse, ein duesenburg, Elle Pollack, Elle74 Zaftig, Emileigh Starbrook, Emma Nowhere, ener bing, Erdrick Balbozar, eric domela, Evangeline Biedermann, Excalibur Longstaff, Fake Fitzgerald, Feldspar Millgrove, Feynt Mistral, Fluf Fredriksson, Forbid Utorid, Fortyniner Beck, Francesco Despres, Francisco Koolhoven, Franta Burt, Fury Rosewood, garde Burrel, Garmin Kawaguichi, Gavin Ichigo, Gellan Glenelg, Genie Demina, Gennifer Meredith, Gigs Taggart, Goldie Katsu, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Haravikk Mistral, Harleen Gretzky, Haruki Watanabe, Heather Manatiso, Henri Beauchamp, Honey Fairweather, Hypatia Callisto, Ice Brodie, icktoofay Kamachi, IntLibber Brautigan, Janise Dreamscape, Jay Shinobu, Jenni Ryba, Jeremy Ondricek, JetZep Zabelin, Jims Smythe, Jini Hammerer, Jopy Weber, JustOneMore Loon, Kaluura Boa, Kara Markova, Kevin Susenko, Khyra Ares, Kii Lilliehook, Kitty Barnett, Kris Kuttelwascher, Lanita Wingtips, Laura18 Streeter, Lee Ludd, Lettrius Jewell, Liberty Tesla, LilyAnna Carter, Lindal Kidd, Lisa Lowe, Lisa McConnell, Lola Machin, luca peck, Lupus Clawtooth, M1sha Dallin, Macsima Dagostino, Mana Janus, Mani Canning, Manjusri Binder, marceledward edman, march Korda, marchino villota, Marcus Llewellyn, MartinRJ Fayray, Matthew Dowd, Max Kleiber, mazzy fastback, McCabe Maxsted, Mckailen Kohnke, Meghan Dench, Melvin Starbrook, Mercia Mcmahon, Miakoda Carnell, Michelle2 Zenovka, Michi Lumin, mick parnall, Milla Michinaga, Millie Thompson, miranda Ashby, Mircea Lobo, MIssSara Beck, mouse mimistrobell, Myria Boa, Nanci Barthelmess, Nargus Asturias, Natalya Debevec, Nedrae Messmer, Nexeus Fatale, Niky Zenovka, Nimrod Szondi, Ninane Yoshikawa, Noch Tripsa, nokithecat writer, Nyko Merlin, Onyx Halberd, oryx tempel, Osprey Therian, Pac Hyun, Panagea McMillan, Patrick Ferrentino, PattehPh0x Katsu, ponk bing, Poppy Linden, Prajna Vella, Precious Rhiano, Prokofy Neva, Randall Lovenkraft, Rascal Ratelle, Raydon Writer, Rhaorth Antonelli, Rock Hayek, Ron Crimson, Ron Khondji, Ronald Richez, Rui Clary, Ruud Lathrop, Sakkano Imako, Sam Reinard, Sascha Vandyke, Scrippy Scofield, Sean18 McCarey, Sedona Mills, Sekonda Huet, Seraph Nephilim, Sergei Milos, Shadowquine Maltz, shai khalifa, sheilah flatley, Sheri Underwood, Shuggy Husky, Sierra Janus, Sigma Avro, Simil Miles, simon kline, Simon Nolan, Sindy Tsure, Sparks Keynes, Squirrel Wood, Stahi Columbia, StarSong Bright, Summer Seale, Sunn Thunders, Susan Koltai, Syler Zhora, Synack Fitzgerald, Tayra Dagostino, Tee Cramer, Teravus Ousley, Thomas Shikami, Tia Araw, Tillie Ariantho, Topher Brooks, Torley Linden, Twosteppin Jewell, tx Oh, urantia jewell, vaguegirl Petty, VeC Merlin, venus petrov, vv33d Beck, vynka dean, zann canto, zeebster colasanti, Zi Ree, Zion Tristan, Zorin Frobozz, Zyzzy Zarf

  3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
  APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
  cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
  expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
  FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
  GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
  Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
  jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
  jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
  ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
  OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
  SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
  SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
  xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
  zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

  All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.

  Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  Happiness is a warm puppy. -- Charles M. Schulz</e_new>
<f_translation>
  Second Life 제작자들: Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Tofu, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Jill, Yool, Jane, Yuki, Yoz, Matthew, Arthur, Jennifer, Karl, Brian, Ben, Janine, Christopher, Madhavi, Everett, Anthony, Joon, Jake, sean, Adreanne, Stephany, KellyJo, Jeremy, Pramod, Joshua, Sean, Christopher, Amy, Ceren, Katherine, jon, Sudheendra, James, Stephan, Kari, Kartic, Todd, Thomas, Joki, Rebecca, Belinda, Bert, Roger, Bridie, Kristi, Brian, Maria, John, Aric, Nathanel, Melinda, Darrell, Jennifer, Sandy, Greg, Rob, Brad, Chris, Eric, Palmer, Asi, Katja, Lisa, Minda, Jen, Aaron, Bryan, Mark, Jonathan, Jamie, Laurel, William, Matthew, Steve, David, Remy, James, Tim, Lee, Brian, Ashlei, Sam, Mike, Ethan, Austin, Wanda, Paul, Brian, Rachel, Valentyn, Emma Williams, Autum, Steven, Laley, Charles, Jessica, Sue, Gillian, CG, Kip, Kristen, Shamiran, Blake, Brett, Erica, Kent, Joel, Plexus, Twilight, Joppa, Enus, Kraft, Naveen, Simon, Q, Ronp, Laurap, Ram, KyleJM, Marty, Kend, Daveh, Prospero, Melissa, Nat, Hamilton, Green, Seraph, Ekim, Miz, Jimmy, Kosmo, Rome, Doris, JT, Benoc, Whump, Mango, Trinity, Patch, TJ, Christy, Bao, Joohwan, Kate, Oreh, Angela, Johan, Cheah, Lan, Matias, Brandy, Cogsworth, Aleks,  Mitchell, Space, Einstein, Bambers, Colton, Malbers, Maggie, Umesh, Santosh, Rose, Stash, Rothman, Winnie, Stella, Niall, 그 외에 많은 분들이 수고해 주셨습니다.

  현재 버전이 최상의 버전이 될 수 있도록 도와주신 게이머 여러분께 감사드립니다: aaron23 decuir, Abelv Vollmar, Abyssin Otoro, ActingIll Igaly, Adamas Carter, Addy Broome, Adelia Menges, Alexandra Rucker, Alexandrea Fride, Alissa Sabre, Alyx Jonson, Ann Otoole, Anton Fargis, Aradia Dielli, Araina jewell, Arcane Clawtooth, arcangelo vantelli, Are Sperber, Argent Stonecutter, arkady yost, Ashcroft Burnham, Ashen Arida, Auron Forcella, Azadine Umarov, Azildin Furst, Balp Allen, Balpien Hammerer, Barney Boomslang, Barrett Slade, becky pippen, Beeflin Grut, Beer Dailey, Behemoth Greenwood, bigmanu greene, bitova loon, Bonca Chikuwa, Bonnie Bechir, Brandon Catteneo, buttonpusher jones, Carina Raymaker, Ceera Murakami, Celierra Darling, ChatNoir Moonsoo, Cheetah Hammerer, chet neurocam, Cinthya Loveless, Cold Spitteler, Coral Quinnell, Crash Pointe, CrazyTB Oh, Creem Pye, Crom Chaffe, ctrl althouse, dade carver, Dael Ra, dakota schwade, Dale Innis, Damian McLeod, Danger Lytton, danielluh ashton, DanOfWA Flanagan, Davec Horsforth, Davidius Morigi, davie zinner, Day Oh, DBDigital Epsilon, Deany Fall, deBruce Munro, Decaf Coffey, Dedric Mauriac, Deeso Saeed, Dekka Raymaker, dexter eberhart, Dildo Spitz, Dizzy Banjo, djcabello klaar, Dnali Anabuki, Domchi Underwood, Doran Zemlja, Drew Dwi, Duckless Vandyke, Duncan Stenvaag, Dylan Rickenbacker, dzogchen Moody, Dzonatas Sol, Eddy Stryker, Edward Griffith, Edward Pearse, ein duesenburg, Elle Pollack, Elle74 Zaftig, Emileigh Starbrook, Emma Nowhere, ener bing, Erdrick Balbozar, eric domela, Evangeline Biedermann, Excalibur Longstaff, Fake Fitzgerald, Feldspar Millgrove, Feynt Mistral, Fluf Fredriksson, Forbid Utorid, Fortyniner Beck, Francesco Despres, Francisco Koolhoven, Franta Burt, Fury Rosewood, garde Burrel, Garmin Kawaguichi, Gavin Ichigo, Gellan Glenelg, Genie Demina, Gennifer Meredith, Gigs Taggart, Goldie Katsu, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Haravikk Mistral, Harleen Gretzky, Haruki Watanabe, Heather Manatiso, Henri Beauchamp, Honey Fairweather, Hypatia Callisto, Ice Brodie, icktoofay Kamachi, IntLibber Brautigan, Janise Dreamscape, Jay Shinobu, Jenni Ryba, Jeremy Ondricek, JetZep Zabelin, Jims Smythe, Jini Hammerer, Jopy Weber, JustOneMore Loon, Kaluura Boa, Kara Markova, Kevin Susenko, Khyra Ares, Kii Lilliehook, Kitty Barnett, Kris Kuttelwascher, Lanita Wingtips, Laura18 Streeter, Lee Ludd, Lettrius Jewell, Liberty Tesla, LilyAnna Carter, Lindal Kidd, Lisa Lowe, Lisa McConnell, Lola Machin, luca peck, Lupus Clawtooth, M1sha Dallin, Macsima Dagostino, Mana Janus, Mani Canning, Manjusri Binder, marceledward edman, march Korda, marchino villota, Marcus Llewellyn, MartinRJ Fayray, Matthew Dowd, Max Kleiber, mazzy fastback, McCabe Maxsted, Mckailen Kohnke, Meghan Dench, Melvin Starbrook, Mercia Mcmahon, Miakoda Carnell, Michelle2 Zenovka, Michi Lumin, mick parnall, Milla Michinaga, Millie Thompson, miranda Ashby, Mircea Lobo, MIssSara Beck, mouse mimistrobell, Myria Boa, Nanci Barthelmess, Nargus Asturias, Natalya Debevec, Nedrae Messmer, Nexeus Fatale, Niky Zenovka, Nimrod Szondi, Ninane Yoshikawa, Noch Tripsa, nokithecat writer, Nyko Merlin, Onyx Halberd, oryx tempel, Osprey Therian, Pac Hyun, Panagea McMillan, Patrick Ferrentino, PattehPh0x Katsu, ponk bing, Poppy Linden, Prajna Vella, Precious Rhiano, Prokofy Neva, Randall Lovenkraft, Rascal Ratelle, Raydon Writer, Rhaorth Antonelli, Rock Hayek, Ron Crimson, Ron Khondji, Ronald Richez, Rui Clary, Ruud Lathrop, Sakkano Imako, Sam Reinard, Sascha Vandyke, Scrippy Scofield, Sean18 McCarey, Sedona Mills, Sekonda Huet, Seraph Nephilim, Sergei Milos, Shadowquine Maltz, shai khalifa, sheilah flatley, Sheri Underwood, Shuggy Husky, Sierra Janus, Sigma Avro, Simil Miles, simon kline, Simon Nolan, Sindy Tsure, Sparks Keynes, Squirrel Wood, Stahi Columbia, StarSong Bright, Summer Seale, Sunn Thunders, Susan Koltai, Syler Zhora, Synack Fitzgerald, Tayra Dagostino, Tee Cramer, Teravus Ousley, Thomas Shikami, Tia Araw, Tillie Ariantho, Topher Brooks, Torley Linden, Twosteppin Jewell, tx Oh, urantia jewell, vaguegirl Petty, VeC Merlin, venus petrov, vv33d Beck, vynka dean, zann canto, zeebster colasanti, Zi Ree, Zion Tristan, Zorin Frobozz, Zyzzy Zarf

  3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
  APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
  cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
  expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
  FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
  GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
  Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
  jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
  jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
  ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
  OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
  SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
  SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
  xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
  zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

  저작권 보유.  자세한 내용은 licenses.txt를 참조하십시오.

  음성 채팅 오디오 코딩: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  행복이란 포근한 강아지 한마리다. -- Charles M. Schulz</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>
		Second Life 제작자들: Philip, Andrew, Tessa, Cory, Frank, James, Doug, Hunter, Richard, John, Eric, Avi, AaronB, AaronY, Ian, Peter, Mark, Robin, Stephen, Tracy, Ryan, Alberto, Haney, Tanya, JimJ, Dan, Ben, Stephanie, Tim, Evan, Catherine, Colin, Chris, Reuben, Charity, Jeska, James, JonHenry, Kelly, Callum, Char, Daniel, DavidF, Don, Jeff, Lauren, Lee, Michael, Ramzi, Vektor, Steve, TomY, Tess, Kona, Brent, Clarissa, PeterP, Jesse, Annette, Cyn, Blue, Ginsu, Jonathan, Karen, Adam, Nova, Deana, Lizzie, Patsy, DavidK, Isaac, Pathfinder, Monroe, Jill, Benny, Altruima, Rheya, Jennifer, Jack, DaveP, Brad, Mick, Babbage, Elisabeth, Brian, Beth, Data, Ethan, Wendy, Nicole, Sky, Jeffrey, Zero, Coffee, Tesla, Kenny, Makiko, Nigel, Teeple, Lucy, Mia, Dee, Guy, Harry, Liana, Branka, Jimbo, Aura, Vasuda, SarahD, bethanye, Torley, Runitai, MikeS, PaulM, Milo, Hermia, JoeM, Melanie, Rejean, DSmith, SMiller, Susan, Jose, DongYun, Justin, Andrey, Syrah, Donovan, Henrik, Nora, Lexie, AC, Donna, ChrisC, Alex, Leyla, Kyle, Mathew, Devin, Joshua, DanC, Jessica, Harmony, Claudia, Tramel, Glenn, Betsy, Fritz, Jun, Adam, Cassandra, Ken, RyanW, Spike, Tofu, Varas, Andy, Luke, RobLa, Chiyo, JohnZ, Dustin, George, Del, PeterP, Migyeong, Matthew, RMullane, CChampion, JTurbin, JamesC, Viola, Lightfoot, Jacqui, Sturm, Adrian, Buttercup, Alfred, Sunil, Alfred, Noel, Irfan, Jill, Yool, Jane, Yuki, Yoz, Matthew, Arthur, Jennifer, Karl, Brian, Ben, Janine, Christopher, Madhavi, Everett, Anthony, Joon, Jake, sean, Adreanne, Stephany, KellyJo, Jeremy, Pramod, Joshua, Sean, Christopher, Amy, Ceren, Katherine, jon, Sudheendra, James, Stephan, Kari, Kartic, Todd, Thomas, Joki, Rebecca, Belinda, Bert, Roger, Bridie, Kristi, Brian, Maria, John, Aric, Nathanel, Melinda, Darrell, Jennifer, Sandy, Greg, Rob, Brad, Chris, Eric, Palmer, Asi, Katja, Lisa, Minda, Jen, Aaron, Bryan, Mark, Jonathan, Jamie, Laurel, William, Matthew, Steve, David, Remy, James, Tim, Lee, Brian, Ashlei, Sam, Mike, Ethan, Austin, Wanda, Paul, Brian, Rachel, Valentyn, Emma Williams, Autum, Steven, Laley, Charles, Jessica, Sue, Gillian, CG, Kip, Kristen, Shamiran, Blake, Brett, Erica, Kent, Joel, Plexus, Twilight, Joppa, Enus, Kraft, Naveen, Simon, Q, Ronp, Laurap, Ram, KyleJM, Marty, Kend, Daveh, Prospero, Melissa, Nat, Hamilton, Green, Seraph, Ekim, Miz, Jimmy, Kosmo, Rome, Doris, JT, Benoc, Whump, Mango, Trinity, Patch, TJ, Christy, Bao, Joohwan, Kate, Oreh, Angela, Johan, Cheah, Lan, Matias, Brandy, Cogsworth, Aleks,  Mitchell, Space, Einstein, Bambers, Colton, Malbers, Maggie, Umesh, Santosh, Rose, Stash, Rothman, Winnie, Stella, Niall, 그 외에 많은 분들이 수고해 주셨습니다.

현재 버전이 최상의 버전이 될 수 있도록 도와주신 게이머 여러분께 감사드립니다: aaron23 decuir, Abelv Vollmar, Abyssin Otoro, ActingIll Igaly, Adamas Carter, Addy Broome, Adelia Menges, Alexandra Rucker, Alexandrea Fride, Alissa Sabre, Alyx Jonson, Ann Otoole, Anton Fargis, Aradia Dielli, Araina jewell, Arcane Clawtooth, arcangelo vantelli, Are Sperber, Argent Stonecutter, arkady yost, Ashcroft Burnham, Ashen Arida, Auron Forcella, Azadine Umarov, Azildin Furst, Balp Allen, Balpien Hammerer, Barney Boomslang, Barrett Slade, becky pippen, Beeflin Grut, Beer Dailey, Behemoth Greenwood, bigmanu greene, bitova loon, Bonca Chikuwa, Bonnie Bechir, Brandon Catteneo, buttonpusher jones, Carina Raymaker, Ceera Murakami, Celierra Darling, ChatNoir Moonsoo, Cheetah Hammerer, chet neurocam, Cinthya Loveless, Cold Spitteler, Coral Quinnell, Crash Pointe, CrazyTB Oh, Creem Pye, Crom Chaffe, ctrl althouse, dade carver, Dael Ra, dakota schwade, Dale Innis, Damian McLeod, Danger Lytton, danielluh ashton, DanOfWA Flanagan, Davec Horsforth, Davidius Morigi, davie zinner, Day Oh, DBDigital Epsilon, Deany Fall, deBruce Munro, Decaf Coffey, Dedric Mauriac, Deeso Saeed, Dekka Raymaker, dexter eberhart, Dildo Spitz, Dizzy Banjo, djcabello klaar, Dnali Anabuki, Domchi Underwood, Doran Zemlja, Drew Dwi, Duckless Vandyke, Duncan Stenvaag, Dylan Rickenbacker, dzogchen Moody, Dzonatas Sol, Eddy Stryker, Edward Griffith, Edward Pearse, ein duesenburg, Elle Pollack, Elle74 Zaftig, Emileigh Starbrook, Emma Nowhere, ener bing, Erdrick Balbozar, eric domela, Evangeline Biedermann, Excalibur Longstaff, Fake Fitzgerald, Feldspar Millgrove, Feynt Mistral, Fluf Fredriksson, Forbid Utorid, Fortyniner Beck, Francesco Despres, Francisco Koolhoven, Franta Burt, Fury Rosewood, garde Burrel, Garmin Kawaguichi, Gavin Ichigo, Gellan Glenelg, Genie Demina, Gennifer Meredith, Gigs Taggart, Goldie Katsu, Gwyneth Llewelyn, Haravikk Mistral, Harleen Gretzky, Haruki Watanabe, Heather Manatiso, Henri Beauchamp, Honey Fairweather, Hypatia Callisto, Ice Brodie, icktoofay Kamachi, IntLibber Brautigan, Janise Dreamscape, Jay Shinobu, Jenni Ryba, Jeremy Ondricek, JetZep Zabelin, Jims Smythe, Jini Hammerer, Jopy Weber, JustOneMore Loon, Kaluura Boa, Kara Markova, Kevin Susenko, Khyra Ares, Kii Lilliehook, Kitty Barnett, Kris Kuttelwascher, Lanita Wingtips, Laura18 Streeter, Lee Ludd, Lettrius Jewell, Liberty Tesla, LilyAnna Carter, Lindal Kidd, Lisa Lowe, Lisa McConnell, Lola Machin, luca peck, Lupus Clawtooth, M1sha Dallin, Macsima Dagostino, Mana Janus, Mani Canning, Manjusri Binder, marceledward edman, march Korda, marchino villota, Marcus Llewellyn, MartinRJ Fayray, Matthew Dowd, Max Kleiber, mazzy fastback, McCabe Maxsted, Mckailen Kohnke, Meghan Dench, Melvin Starbrook, Mercia Mcmahon, Miakoda Carnell, Michelle2 Zenovka, Michi Lumin, mick parnall, Milla Michinaga, Millie Thompson, miranda Ashby, Mircea Lobo, MIssSara Beck, mouse mimistrobell, Myria Boa, Nanci Barthelmess, Nargus Asturias, Natalya Debevec, Nedrae Messmer, Nexeus Fatale, Niky Zenovka, Nimrod Szondi, Ninane Yoshikawa, Noch Tripsa, nokithecat writer, Nyko Merlin, Onyx Halberd, oryx tempel, Osprey Therian, Pac Hyun, Panagea McMillan, Patrick Ferrentino, PattehPh0x Katsu, ponk bing, Poppy Linden, Prajna Vella, Precious Rhiano, Prokofy Neva, Randall Lovenkraft, Rascal Ratelle, Raydon Writer, Rhaorth Antonelli, Rock Hayek, Ron Crimson, Ron Khondji, Ronald Richez, Rui Clary, Ruud Lathrop, Sakkano Imako, Sam Reinard, Sascha Vandyke, Scrippy Scofield, Sean18 McCarey, Sedona Mills, Sekonda Huet, Seraph Nephilim, Sergei Milos, Shadowquine Maltz, shai khalifa, sheilah flatley, Sheri Underwood, Shuggy Husky, Sierra Janus, Sigma Avro, Simil Miles, simon kline, Simon Nolan, Sindy Tsure, Sparks Keynes, Squirrel Wood, Stahi Columbia, StarSong Bright, Summer Seale, Sunn Thunders, Susan Koltai, Syler Zhora, Synack Fitzgerald, Tayra Dagostino, Tee Cramer, Teravus Ousley, Thomas Shikami, Tia Araw, Tillie Ariantho, Topher Brooks, Torley Linden, Twosteppin Jewell, tx Oh, urantia jewell, vaguegirl Petty, VeC Merlin, venus petrov, vv33d Beck, vynka dean, zann canto, zeebster colasanti, Zi Ree, Zion Tristan, Zorin Frobozz, Zyzzy Zarf

APR Copyright (C) 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2001, Xiphophorus
OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

저작권 보유.  자세한 내용은 licenses.txt를 참조하십시오.

음성 채팅 오디오 코딩: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


행복이란 포근한 강아지 한마리다. -- Charles M. Schulz
	</f_old_trans>
</string><string><a_file>alerts.xml</a_file>
<b_path>//GraphicsPreferencesHelp/message</b_path>
<c_attribute></c_attribute>
<d_old>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The graphics preferences interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. One may customize their graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amout of detail used in rendering certain objects.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of terrain detail you would like to see. 

Sky Detail: Sets the amount of tesselation of the sky dome.  A higher value takes longer to render, but makes the sun look more rounded.
		</d_old>
<e_new>
			This panel controls window size and resolution and the quality of the client&apos;s graphics.  The Preferences &gt; Graphics interface allows you to choose between four graphics levels: Low, Mid, High, and Ultra. You may also customize your graphics settings by checking the Custom checkbox and manipulating the following settings:

Shaders: Enable or disable various types of pixel shaders. 

Reflection Detail: Sets the types of objects that water can reflect.

Avatar Rendering: Sets options that affect how the client renders avatars.

Draw Distance: Affects how far out from your viewpoint objects will be rendered in the scene.

Max Particle Count: Sets the maximum number of particles you are able to see on your screen at once.

Post Process Quality: Sets the resolution with which Glow is rendered. 

Mesh Detail: Sets the amount of detail or number of triangles used in rendering certain objects. A higher value takes longer to render, but makes these objects appear with more detail.

Lighting Detail: Selects what types of lights you would like to render.

Terrain Detail: Sets the amount of detail you would like to see for the terrain texture. 
		</e_new>
<f_old_trans></f_old_trans>
<f_translation>
			세컨드라이프 클라이언트의 그래픽 해상도 및 품질을 제어합니다.  낮음, 중간, 높음, 매우 높음  4단계의 설정을  선택할 수 있습니다. 또한 사용자 크기 확인란을 선택 후 설정을 세부 조작할 수 있습니다.

쉐이더: 쉐이더 유형을 활성화하거나 비활성화합니다. 

반사 디테일: 물에 반사되는 오브젝트 유형을 설정합니다.

아바타 렌더링: 아바타를 렌더링하는 방식의 옵션을 설정합니다.

렌더링 거리 제한: 현재 시점에서 부터 오브젝트가 렌더링되는 거리를 조절합니다.

최대 파티클 수: 화면에서 한 번에 볼 수 있는 최대 파티클 수를 설정합니다.

빛 처리 품질: 빛이 렌더링되는 해상도를 설정합니다. 

메쉬 디테일: 특정 오브젝트를 렌더링하는 디테일 또는 삼각형 개수를 설정합니다. 값이 클수록 렌더링이 더 오래 걸리지만 오브젝트의 모양이 더 자세하게 표현됩니다.

조명 세부 사항: 조명의 유형을 선택합니다.

지형 세부 사항: 지형 텍스처의 디테일을 설정합니다. 
		</f_translation>
<f_old_trans>
			이 창은 창 크기와 클라이언트 그래픽의 해상도 및 품질을 제어합니다.  그래픽 환경 설정 인터페이스를 통해 낮음, 중간, 높음, 매우 높음 등 4개의 그래픽 레벨 중에서 원하는 설정을 선택할 수 있습니다. 사용자 지정 확인란을 선택하고 다음의 설정을 조작하여 이러한 그래픽을 원하는 대로 설정할 수 있습니다.

쉐이더: 여러 가지 픽셀 쉐이더 유형을 활성화하거나 비활성화합니다. 

반사 디테일: 물에 반사될 수 있는 오브젝트 유형을 설정합니다.

아바타 렌더링: 클라이언트가 아바타를 렌더링하는 방식에 영향을 주는 옵션을 설정합니다.

렌더링 거리 제한: 장면에서 현재 시점의 오브젝트가 렌더링되는 거리를 조절합니다.

최대 파티클 수: 화면에서 한 번에 볼 수 있는 최대 파티클 수를 설정합니다.

빛 처리 품질: 빛이 렌더링되는 해상도를 설정합니다. 

메쉬 디테일: 오브젝트를 렌더링하는 디테일을 설정합니다.

조명 세부 사항: 렌더링할 조명 유형을 선택합니다.

지형 세부 사항: 보려는 지형의 디테일을 설정합니다. 
		</f_old_trans>
</string>
</strings>
